<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

 <title>Nico Boyce</title>
 <link href="https://nicoboyce.com/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
 <link href="https://nicoboyce.com/"/>
 <updated>2026-02-02T10:40:43+00:00</updated>
 <id>https://nicoboyce.com</id>
 <author>
   <name>Nico Beastie Boyce</name>
   <email></email>
 </author>

 
 <entry>
   <title>Days, in 35mm slices</title>
   <link href="https://nicoboyce.com/snaps/2026/01/15/days-in-35mm-slices/"/>
   <updated>2026-01-15T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
   <id>https://nicoboyce.com/snaps/2026/01/15/days-in-35mm-slices</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;I’m obviously not quite busy enough so why not revisit the problems of the past to make hobbies even more expensive and time consuming?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve been using this pretty much exclusively for the last couple of months. It’s chunky and clunky and old. It’s opinionated about the way things should be done. It can be a bit frustrating and temperamental. It’s hard to know why I feel something for this tool.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/nikon-f601.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Nikon.&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Nikon F-601.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The camera gear situation is getting a bit silly here lately. I have sold some lenses and the Fuji X-H2 but it’s definitely excessive nevertheless. Here is some of the stuff.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/cameras.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;Cameras.&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Cameras.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anyway more interesting probably is what’s coming out of the camera. I’ve used it for a range of photography and with a mix of Fuji and Kodak film. I’m getting everything developed by &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.thefilmsafe.co.uk/?nicoboycedotcom&quot;&gt;The Film Safe&lt;/a&gt; who are just delightful. Which are your favourite shots?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/35mm/bhtruck.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;BH Truck.&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;BH Truck.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/35mm/closed.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;Closed.&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Closed.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/35mm/crow.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Crow.&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Crow.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/35mm/dawlish.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Dawlish.&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Dawlish.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/35mm/portsdown.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Portsdown.&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Portsdown.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/35mm/splash.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;Splash.&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Splash.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/35mm/track.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;Track.&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Track.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Yes, I have been rollerblading a lot</title>
   <link href="https://nicoboyce.com/2026/01/06/rolling/"/>
   <updated>2026-01-06T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
   <id>https://nicoboyce.com/2026/01/06/rolling</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;now I’m going to talk about it&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rollerblading is a polarising thing to do. I can’t think of many other hobbies which draw so much comment from passers-by. If you like to keep a low profile, if you like to avoid talking to strangers, don’t do rollerblading.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/solent.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;By the sea.&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;By the sea.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I used to love rolling around as a kid. It was interrupted by injuries&lt;!--excerpt-end--&gt; (I broke my arm twice when I was nine) and other interests came along at 12. We’re talking Magic the Gathering, Quake 3, Terry Pratchett. Oh also I learned to ride a bike about that time. Before 12 though, there were about four years where being outside meant being on tiny wheels.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;By the end I was pretty good! I could skate backwards pretty much as quick as forwards, I got picked for a roller hockey team, I had plenty of good times on my blades. It’s okay to grow up.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;now-it-turns-out-being-grown-isnt-all-great&quot;&gt;Now it turns out being grown isn’t all great&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think I’m doing pretty well at being an adult. I do a job I enjoy and it funds doing plenty of fun stuff. I’ve got nice adult toys (no not in that sense, you sleaze) like &lt;a href=&quot;https://nicoboyce.com/essays/2025/04/22/releasing-music-for-drecks/&quot;&gt;guitars&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://nicoboyce.com/gear/&quot;&gt;camping kit&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://nicoboyce.com/snaps/&quot;&gt;photography&lt;/a&gt; gear and &lt;a href=&quot;https://nicoboyce.com/wheels/2024/09/01/e30-m25-birthday-present/&quot;&gt;the BMW&lt;/a&gt;. On the other hand, I’m only getting older! No amount of sim racing gear or guitar pedals will slow that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So why not treat myself and take up skating again, with the kind of set-up I would have loved as a kid?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;There’s no reason, the question was rhetorical&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So I grabbed some from a charity shop (which happened to be the same boots as the ones I had as a kid! Obviously a tad bigger now) but it turns out I’m a bit more sophisticated (and heavy) than I was at that age and I needed something better.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here’s what I’m rolling on lately:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/skates.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Skates.&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Skates.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They are a pretty great ride!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;this-is-all-fun-and-games-but-im-only-here-for-the-tech-specs&quot;&gt;This is all fun and games but I’m only here for the tech specs&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m rolling on &lt;strong&gt;Roces M12 UFS Lo&lt;/strong&gt; with some modifications.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Roces have apparently existed since 1952. I wasn’t around then but I will take their word for it. The M12 boot was launched in 1996, so it was the latest and greatest when I was starting! I would have loved some then. I love these now instead!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;UFS is the Universal Frame System. Yes, the rollerskate companies agreed on some basic compatibility long before anyone even dared to ask Apple to make any effort to co-operate with other PC manufacturers. It just specifies a couple of mount points on the sole and the dimensions of the frame, which is the piece the wheels are mounted in.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lo on the Roces means that the cuff and the liner don’t go so high up your calf at the back. This is a preference thing. The liner in these boots is a basic one from Loco Skates.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The stock Roces frame is probably great if you’re under 40kg but I had two issues with it. The middle wheels are “antirocker” types, which means they are actually just spacers really. They don’t roll and don’t have bearings in them. Again, this is probably fine for kids and people who are very serious about rollerblading but I’m a busy dad who eats too many biscuits.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Additionally, the stock frame is quite flexible. I think it’s made of nylon and I didn’t have much confidence on it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;a-word-on-configurations&quot;&gt;A word on configurations&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Antirocker wheels are called that because your first and fourth wheel on each boot wear down much quicker and so if you have equal wheels (flat configuration) then you end up with a bit of a rocking sensation as your foot seesaws over the middle wheels. This feels bad, so antirocker exists.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/roces.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Antirocker.&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Antirocker.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you want a flat setup (i.e. four equal wheels) then you need to periodically swap the positions of your wheels around to prevent it becoming a rocker.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can also get a “freestyle” configuration where you just take out the middle wheels and so have two wheels on each boot. This is lighter but you lose grip on tight turns or hard stops.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some people do ride a rocker setup apparently. Weirdos.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;modifications&quot;&gt;Modifications&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I added a foam insole of some sort to help my weird feet. Plastic boots need plenty of padding whoever you are though.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The laces are now these really classy yellow ones. They match…all of my things. A great style upgrade.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/roces2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Laces.&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Laces.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The stock wheels (though not the inside wheels remember) were Revolver branded. I think they are 64mm and 88a hardness rated. They have a very round profile. It felt to me like I was on stilts and there wasn’t much rubber on the road. I switched them for some Iqon wheels which were 55mm 85a and have a square profile, so a large contact patch. These are indoor wheels really, so they have super high rolling resistance and you feel every molecule of imperfection in the road.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve now swapped the frames for 50-50 Prime frames. Rosie got me these for a present and I am very happy with them. Each boot is a little heavier but the frame has an aluminium structure and feels absolutely rock solid. It has given me the confidence to put the Revolver wheels on the front and back and the Iqon wheels in the middle positions, which honestly feels so great!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/skating.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;Skating time.&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Skating time.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m rolling on Bones bearings and they are okay but honestly I hoped for more from them. Fancy ABEC 9 bearings on the outside wheels at least would be the next thing to do.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a straight line, there’s much less rolling resistance so it is less difficult to get moving. On a turn, the middle wheels with their softer rubber and flatter profile really help bite into the tarmac and turn me around.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;so-what&quot;&gt;So what?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hey, this is my website and I’ll talk about rollerskating if I want to. And if that makes you want to throw things at me, well I’m still laughing because I’ve got this classy helmet!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/lid.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Helmet.&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Helmet.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>2025 is over</title>
   <link href="https://nicoboyce.com/2025/12/31/it-is-over/"/>
   <updated>2025-12-31T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
   <id>https://nicoboyce.com/2025/12/31/it-is-over</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;wow that was a time wasn’t it&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So yes today is the LAST DAY OF THE YEAR and so here are some thoughts which I have had on various topics. Do you agree? Do you disagree? That’s okay!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;music-sounds-etc&quot;&gt;Music, sounds, etc&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I guess for a lot of people 2025 was about waiting in virtual queues hoping to get tickets to big stadium shows from lowest common denominator pop acts. I’m not mad at you if you are in to that, I’m just disappointed and let’s not speak about it further.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We saw some really great stuff. Have A Nice Life. Divide And Dissolve. Earth. The Beta Band! High On Fire (plus incredible supports including Castle Rat) and I’m sure I’m forgetting so many excellent other bands. Queens of the Stone Age a couple of times.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve heard people say don’t meet your heroes. They need to choose their heroes better. I’ve met pretty much all of my musical idols and they were almost all absolutely lovely.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/earth.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Earth.&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Dylan Carlson of Earth.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;how-about-new-music&quot;&gt;How about new music?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So 2025 was a year where artists whose work I had been enjoying over the last few years released records which made me go “oh okay, that’s a shame.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here are some of those:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Earl Sweatshirt&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Simz&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Ikonika&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;FKA Twigs&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;JPEGMAFIA&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Divide And Dissolve&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Princess Nokia&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Yaya Bey&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Masters of Reality&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;None of these were bad! They were all fine but just not super great.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anyone who had Eusexua on their best-of lists honestly probably just hasn’t recently revisited the best stuff Madonna and Bjork did in the 1990s.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While collating this list I made a note that I need to put some more time in to the newest Clipping and Kae Tempest records.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My favourite new record this year was PinkPanteress mixtape Fancy That and my favourite new song of the year was Music by Underscores and nothing else really came close to those choices for me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Finally I’ve got to say “go and listen to Esdeekid” if you’re not yet in on that thing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;live-highlights&quot;&gt;Live highlights?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My favourite performance I got to experience this year is a bit more tough. I’m going to pick individual songs from shows, why not.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Bees Made Honey in the Lion’s Skull by Earth at the Electric Ballroom was like the whole world was revolving around the incredible patience of drummer Adrienne. Teased out over what felt like hours, this rendition of this track was so powerful I don’t know how we made it home afterwards.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Queens of the Stone Age, Long Slow Goodbye at the Royal Albert Hall. I didn’t have Josh Homme waving a hatchett around and Matt Berry pulling out all the stops on the monstrous RAH organ on my bingo card for the year.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Beta Band, Dry the Rain. This was at the Roundhouse. It felt like a strange moment in my life. The two decades since their last shows, one of the first proper gigs I made it to, all of that seemed forgiven in that moment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;tv-cinema-audiovisual-media&quot;&gt;TV, cinema, audiovisual media&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am always saying I don’t feel like film is a great way to tell a story. Nothing in 2025 has changed my view on that. I have really struggled (and I have failed) to think of anything new I didn’t hate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;films-ie-long-form-storytelling&quot;&gt;Films (i.e. long form storytelling)&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The M word for films makes me feel a bit nauseous, like people get about words like “touch” and “moist” so I don’t say it. I think it might be because it sounds like something a toddler would say if they didn’t know the right word? Anyway, I hate it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m a big motorsports fan and I think women are people so of course I watched and loathed that F1 film. It was painful to endure and I don’t understand why through the editing process no one said “this is embarrassing and we need to make this better” but I’m sure it earned plenty of cash.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The live action remake of Lilo and Stitch was unneccesary but basically fine and I thought the performance of the little girl was great. Shame not to get Ving Rames and I’m not sure why they added the portal gun from the Portal games but I like the Portal games and it was fun.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The other day we saw the Spongebob film and there were things about it which were pretty alright. I expected that to be a miserable couple of hours for me sat there but the nods to Greek myths and Mark Hamill was enough to keep me engaged.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m sure I saw some other new films but I don’t remember them. Honestly I don’t really care about films (outside of Takeshi Kitano gangster films) and if you want film recommendations then probably ask someone else.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;something-positive-though&quot;&gt;Something positive though&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There is some incredible work going on by people who don’t have the BBC or Netflix funding them but they just have something to say. I’m thinking of people like Josh Johnson, whose output has been just incredible through the year. Television and cinema are basically over but we don’t need the gatekeepers, just a camera and some time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;motorsport&quot;&gt;Motorsport&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I felt like 2025 was quite a sad year for motorsport in general. The FIA and NASCAR organisations have their reputations absolutely in the toilet now. This doesn’t take away from some amazing performances by drivers and teams though.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/truck.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Truck.&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;British Truck Racing Championship. Brands Hatch.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Go and see some motorsport near you. It’s a great day out!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;single-seaters&quot;&gt;Single seaters&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;McLaren muddled over the line but the drivers need to tell the team that the perception of fairness is not as important as winning. At times it felt like Mac strategy was designed to give Max a chance!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Indycar never looked particularly close this year. I didn’t much like Will Buxton on the coverage. I’m glad Penske had such rotten results but otherwise there was little to be excited about.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Formula 2 was a mixed bag. There were some fun races but apart from the champ Fornaroli the whole field had such inconsistent performance that I can’t see any of these guys being world champions of the future. Dunne really faded but an absolute shocker was Gabriele Minì. F3 was much the same. I wonder if it’s because the costs are so high and the seasons so long.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I didn’t really follow British F4 this year or regional F3/F4 championships.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;endurance-sports-cars-etc&quot;&gt;Endurance, sports cars, etc.&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;IMSA was great this year, full of excitement and great coverage. I am super into the AO Racing team with their dinosaur themed cars and getting the kids excited, making great merch and then throwing everything at the performances. The Vasser Sullivan team gets my respect too, turning up year after year with that ancient Lexus GT3 (that car was launched in 2014!) and achieving great things.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a bonus IMSA has the best support series on the planet, the MX-5 cup, as well as the best commentary team in John and Shea.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s a great time to get into enduros as Verstappen draws attention to the Nurburgring and more manufacturers join the WEC.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;People ask me how you enjoy endurance racing. It’s a strange thing to get in to! Basically you pop it up on a screen and get on with what you’re doing, looking over when you hear some excitement, tuning in and out as you please. It’s like test cricket a bit. You can sit and take in an hour here and there but you don’t sit and stare for the full event. Maybe I’ll write a full essay about how to enjoy enduros but that’s the gist. Daytona soon!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;rally-rallycross&quot;&gt;Rally, rallycross&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The WRC was really hot this year. I’ve never been a big fan of watching rallies. They are great to drive in but they aren’t made for television. The WRC was great this year. I’m worried about next year with two of the top drivers quitting.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rallycross had such a terrible year. It’s my favourite racing format but there just seems to be no way of making it sustainable. I don’t understand how no one makes a success of it, because RX is perfect for TV and really fun for more casual fans. RIP to WorldRX, Nitrocross, Extreme E.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But let’s not worry about that right now. Just make sure you’re watching the British RX and also RallyX.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now the W2RC is the craziest thing in the world I’m sure and I am still in shock at Nassar losing the title over a timing technicality. The Dakar is coming up and you need to make sure you’re catching those daily highlights.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;random-car-bits&quot;&gt;Random car bits&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was glad Tom Ingram got it done in the BTCC. One of the nicest racing drivers I’ve met, so much time for everyone. I remember when he was posting on his Facebook every week trying desperately to get helo funding the next weekend of racing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The British Hillclimbing has been great fun. You’ve got to get to an event near you, it’s so much fun in person. The commentary team on youtube are excellent too.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I guess read this if you haven’t: &lt;a href=&quot;https://nicoboyce.com/wheels/2025/08/10/racing-worth-watching/&quot;&gt;Racing worth watching&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;stop-reading-here&quot;&gt;Stop reading here&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is the end of the article (I might start putting this on everything I write)&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Nico vanity shots of 2025</title>
   <link href="https://nicoboyce.com/snaps/2025/12/29/nico-vanity-shots-of-2025/"/>
   <updated>2025-12-29T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
   <id>https://nicoboyce.com/snaps/2025/12/29/nico-vanity-shots-of-2025</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/nbb/nbb-bmx.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;BMX.&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;BMX.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/nbb/nbb-cold.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Cold.&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Cold.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/nbb/nbb-como.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Como.&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Como.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/nbb/nbb-conference.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Conference.&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Conference.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/nbb/nbb-gb.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;GB.&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Geckoboard. &lt;a href=&quot;www.youtube.com/watch?v=rN7V9Q1XHvY&quot;&gt;Watch us here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/nbb/nbb-london.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;London.&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;London.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/nbb/nbb-photography.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Photography.&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Photography.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/nbb/nbb-shorn.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Shorn.&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Shorn.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Brands Hatch camera showdown</title>
   <link href="https://nicoboyce.com/wheels/2025/11/09/brands-hatch-camera-showdown/"/>
   <updated>2025-11-09T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
   <id>https://nicoboyce.com/wheels/2025/11/09/brands-hatch-camera-showdown</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;We took a bunch of photography gear to Brands Hatch. One of the cameras was my current favourite toy, this F601 with 75-300mm.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/brands-hatch/nikonf601.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Nikon F601 camera.&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Snap snap!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Representing modernity we had a Fuji XS20, Sigma 16-300mm. In the middle we had a Nikon D3300, 70-300mm. Can you guess which photo was taken with which camera?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/brands-hatch/druids.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;Druids corner action.&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;TCRs struggle for grip at Druids.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/brands-hatch/teeth.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;TCR teeth.&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Tasty TCR.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/brands-hatch/minis.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Mini racing.&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Greasy conditions and front wheel drive means endless understeer.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/brands-hatch/saxo.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Saxo on track.&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Saxo appeal.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/brands-hatch/truck.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Racing truck.&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Heavy metal.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’re looking to get some film developed, give &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.thefilmsafe.co.uk/?hellofromnicoboycedotcom&quot;&gt;The Film Safe&lt;/a&gt; a go. Top people and great results.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Top straight white guy jobs in '25</title>
   <link href="https://nicoboyce.com/2025/09/23/top-straight-white-guy-jobs-25/"/>
   <updated>2025-09-23T00:00:00+01:00</updated>
   <id>https://nicoboyce.com/2025/09/23/top-straight-white-guy-jobs-25</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;h3 id=&quot;or-how-to-unleash-that-secret-talent-youre-sure-you-have-somewhere-big-guy&quot;&gt;or How to unleash that secret talent you’re sure you have somewhere, big guy&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Doing things is hard. Making new things requires understanding existing things. Skills take time to develop, tools need to be mastered, creativity requires imagination. Who can be arsed? Certainly not the straight white guys of the internet!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here are some things they can fall upwards into, despite everything about them.&lt;!--excerpt-end--&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;looking-at-things&quot;&gt;Looking at things&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is a great place to start because the barrier to entry is almost zero. You’re probably reading this on a thing which can take photos, so that saves any initial expenditure. Later you will need a Leica for the little red circle on the front. The process:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;See somthing&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Point the camera at it&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Write a vague caption not related to the image “Sometimes the first step is the hardest” or “When the real enemy is within” etc&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Buy gear.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/snap.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Shooting.&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;What a poseur.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There’s no point where money is likely to fall out but if you grow your hair a bit floppy and tell a lot of people you are a photographer, maybe someone dumb and pretty will let you look at them through a lens. This is literally the dream of every white guy with a Leica, to become a pornographer without having to learn anything or hire sex workers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;listening-to-things&quot;&gt;Listening to things&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Music reviews used to be useful in 1999 when CDs were like £15 (which is probably £40 in 2025 sterling) and your pocket money covered maybe one or two a month. But it’s not 1999 now and everyone has access to basically all of the music basically all of the time. No one needs to read reviews to decide whether they’ll listen to Showbiz or Performance and Cocktails or Californication. You can quickly flick through all three and be judgemental (overwrought juvenile psuedointellectualism, unimaginitive and unambitious, overproduced overwritten earache, respectively) in a shorter time than it would take to find the right issues of NME.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Nevertheless that guy Anthony Fantano is over there and Rick Beato is that way and Christgau still exists (why?) and you could join them if you can bitch your way into a position of presumed authority on a form of media which essentially exists as a utility rather than luxury now.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;See also: that guy booted from comedy rock one hit wonders the Darkness. Youtube suggests him all the time but I never click it. Will it learn?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;playing-video-games&quot;&gt;Playing video games&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Remember how you were always being told to get off your arse and do something because playing video games doesn’t pay the bills? But now she has gone and you watch people you don’t know play games and people give them cash all day! Repeat after me: Fuck you Michelle, you’ll soon see, just as soon as I get some LED triangles for my wall and get good at Rocket League.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;literally-just-whinge-about-stuff&quot;&gt;Literally just whinge about stuff&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Podcasts are back again, again, though now no one has ipods or uses rss but who cares, grab a mic and make sounds!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/recording.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;Talking.&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Talking.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can combine this with anything else (or nothing) so long as you’re talking. Someone is bound to want to listen!&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Visit to Museo della Seta di Como</title>
   <link href="https://nicoboyce.com/snaps/2025/08/23/visit-to-museo-della-seta-di-como/"/>
   <updated>2025-08-23T00:00:00+01:00</updated>
   <id>https://nicoboyce.com/snaps/2025/08/23/visit-to-museo-della-seta-di-como</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/silk/silk1.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;Silk weaving machine.&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/silk/silk2.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;Silk threads.&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/silk/silk3.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;Vintage loom.&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/silk/silk4.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;Silk production tools.&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/silk/silk5.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;Museum display.&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/silk/silk6.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;Historic machinery.&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/silk/silk7.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;Silk processing equipment.&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/silk/silk8.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;Workshop interior.&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Structures</title>
   <link href="https://nicoboyce.com/snaps/2025/08/23/structures/"/>
   <updated>2025-08-23T00:00:00+01:00</updated>
   <id>https://nicoboyce.com/snaps/2025/08/23/structures</id>
   <content type="html">
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/lecco.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Lecco.&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Lecco.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/balconies.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Balconies.&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Balconies.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/wedge.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Wedge.&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Wedge.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/towers.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Towers.&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Towers.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Italian animals</title>
   <link href="https://nicoboyce.com/snaps/2025/08/23/italian-animals/"/>
   <updated>2025-08-23T00:00:00+01:00</updated>
   <id>https://nicoboyce.com/snaps/2025/08/23/italian-animals</id>
   <content type="html">
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/halo.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Halo.&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Halo.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/tucked.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;Tucked.&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Tucked.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/egret.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Egret.&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Egret.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Classy travellers</title>
   <link href="https://nicoboyce.com/wheels/2025/08/23/classy-travellers/"/>
   <updated>2025-08-23T00:00:00+01:00</updated>
   <id>https://nicoboyce.com/wheels/2025/08/23/classy-travellers</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/teeth.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Teeth.&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Teeth.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/chunk.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;Chunk.&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Chunk.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Decision time, brown</title>
   <link href="https://nicoboyce.com/wheels/2025/08/15/lando-needs-therapy/"/>
   <updated>2025-08-15T00:00:00+01:00</updated>
   <id>https://nicoboyce.com/wheels/2025/08/15/lando-needs-therapy</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Lando has more than double the grand prix experience of Oscar but fewer wins. I like Lando. I saw him race at Brands Hatch in the Ginetta Juniors a few years back. He’s a quick boy and it doesn’t hurt that he has boy band looks and good marketing people making the most of that. He needs to spend some of that cash getting his head together.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Until Lando sorts out the mental stuff there’s no chance they’ll be engraving his name on the fancy pot at the end of the year. Mac need to throw their full support behind Oscar and kill off the prospect of a Red Bull resurgence.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Racing worth watching</title>
   <link href="https://nicoboyce.com/wheels/2025/08/10/racing-worth-watching/"/>
   <updated>2025-08-10T00:00:00+01:00</updated>
   <id>https://nicoboyce.com/wheels/2025/08/10/racing-worth-watching</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;If you’re looking to be entertained by cars driven fast, here’s what I enjoy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;in-the-uk&quot;&gt;In the UK&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/@HillClimbTV&quot;&gt;British Hillclimb&lt;/a&gt; (see you at Prescott!)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/@5NationsBRX&quot;&gt;British Rallycross&lt;/a&gt; especially the buggies at Lydden Hill and the 2wd retro cars, always fun&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=gaJu3YiBYVc&quot;&gt;VSCC Lakeland Trial&lt;/a&gt; and honestly any vintage hillclimbs/trials/sprints are excellent&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/@750MotorClubTV&quot;&gt;750 Motor Club&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/@OfficialBTCC&quot;&gt;BTCC&lt;/a&gt; but I’m sure you know that&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/@TheBRSCC/streams&quot;&gt;BRSCC&lt;/a&gt; which is always a great value day out&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;international&quot;&gt;International&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/@imsaofficial/streams&quot;&gt;IMSA&lt;/a&gt;, particularly the MX-5 cup. John and Shea might be the best commentary duo in motorsport.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/@nitrocross/videos&quot;&gt;Nitrocross&lt;/a&gt; formerly Nitro Rallycross. I think this series folded but it’s well worth a watch, especially the 2021 season. Coley and Jared are also great commentators.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/@HillClimbMonsters&quot;&gt;Hillclimb Monsters&lt;/a&gt; is not a series per se but all the craziest hillclimb builds you could want&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/@K4Movies/videos&quot;&gt;K4 Movies&lt;/a&gt; film all the craziest off road events in Europe, from ATVs to 8x8 trucks.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/@G7Media/videos&quot;&gt;Formula Offroad Iceland&lt;/a&gt;, also broadcast by &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/user/jakobcecil&quot;&gt;Jakob Cecil&lt;/a&gt;, is just nuts and commentator Kristian is fantastic.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let me know what I have missed, via &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:hello@nicoboyce.com&quot;&gt;hello@nicoboyce.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Horner had it coming</title>
   <link href="https://nicoboyce.com/wheels/2025/07/11/horner-had-it-coming/"/>
   <updated>2025-07-11T00:00:00+01:00</updated>
   <id>https://nicoboyce.com/wheels/2025/07/11/horner-had-it-coming</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Ecclestone said (I’m paraphrasing) people will put up with you being difficult so long as you’re winning, but the moment that ends then the knives are out.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;No one wants to bump into someone they know from work when they are on holiday but it looks like Toto and Max picked the same spot off of Sardinia to anchor their yachts. Awkward!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With Max at Merc and Horner potentially a free agent eventually (though likely he has to buy out his RBR contract to 2030) we’re faced with the delicious prospect of Horner and Hamilton in red versus Max and Toto in grey. Given how these guys obsess over each other, my money would be on Piastri being a double world champ come the end of ‘26.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve written further nonsense &lt;a href=&quot;https://nicoboyce.com/2025/07/11/christians-tough-day/&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Christian's tough day</title>
   <link href="https://nicoboyce.com/wheels/2025/07/11/christians-tough-day/"/>
   <updated>2025-07-11T00:00:00+01:00</updated>
   <id>https://nicoboyce.com/wheels/2025/07/11/christians-tough-day</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;We’ve all had bad days. Sometimes the problems are of our own making.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve been thinking about this meeting which took place earlier in the week. I think it probably went something like this.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hey Christian, thanks for coming in. Did they offer you a fizzy drink? Okay great&lt;!--excerpt-end--&gt;, let’s jump into it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We just came off of a conference call with Mercedes lawyers and Max Verstappen’s management and they have triggered an exit clause. I couldn’t hear too well, the signal isn’t great from the harbour in Sardinia. He’ll be leaving at the end of the season. He’s the one with the number 1 on his car, is that right?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well anyway it seems we had a big release fee in there so that’ll help balance the books. In the mean time you can look at where you’re putting each of your drivers. I’m sure you’ve planned for this eventuality so we just need to stick to that process. Just like your ongoing court case! Oh sorry, yes, superinjunction, I’ll shush. Scratch that from the minutes!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Oh you’re not sure what the plan is now? That’s okay, I was looking over the notes from last year’s general meeting and you had that Australian chap, right? The one with the big grin and somehow got a win in a McLaren. That team seemed pretty useless last time I came to a race!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/redbull.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;Red Bull car in the paddock at the Thruxton Historic.&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Red Bull car in the paddock at the Thruxton Historic.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;McLaren are the current champions? I thought that was us. Never mind. And we fired the Aussie guy? Seems like we wasted that cash bringing him back but okay. Well who’s next in line then, we’ve still got the Mexican fellow, the one with the big backing?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ah okay well if he wasn’t doing the job then of course he had to go. Shame to lose the sponsorship but at least we’re not paying his salary now! His contract was up at the end of the year as I recall.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We’re still paying him even though we sacked him? That seems a bit…expensive. Isn’t there a spending cap? We gave him a new contract? To encourage him to do better? I don’t pay people more if they get worse, I get someone else! I’m sure we can learn from this. So who else is on the books? Did you ever try out the blonde guy? You said it was worth us funding his F3 and F2 entries.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Didn’t work out, swapped him for Tsunoda, okay it’s a bit cruel but that makes sense. Hey, it’s like the thing you did with your first wife and the Spice Girl! How is she lately? Only talking through the lawyers? Well that’s all good practice for the rest of the season with Max.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I presume Tsunoda has racked up the points, kept Max honest this year. Sounds like we’ll be alright there then, so long as Adrian Newey builds another of those rocketships! How is Adrian by the way, I didn’t see him at the Monaco dinner. He has gone too?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Christian I’m just going to pop out for a minute, I’ve got to check in with the board. Can we get you another fizzy drink?&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Car photo dump, no logic</title>
   <link href="https://nicoboyce.com/wheels/2025/06/15/car-photo-dump/"/>
   <updated>2025-06-15T00:00:00+01:00</updated>
   <id>https://nicoboyce.com/wheels/2025/06/15/car-photo-dump</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/cars/petrol-with-plato.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;Plato&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Petrol with Plato&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/cars/limited-edition-lambo.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;Lambo&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Limited edition Lambo&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/cars/on-the-tank-course.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;Tidworth&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;on the tank course&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/cars/f4-rivals.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;f4&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;F4 rivals&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/cars/michael-andretti-mclaren.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;Mac&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Michael Andretti McLaren&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/cars/marlborough.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;Marlborough&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Marlborough&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/cars/thruxton-test-day.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;Thruxton test day&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Thruxton test day&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/cars/purple-na.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;purple NA&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;purple NA&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/cars/breakfast-club-alfa.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;Alfa&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Breakfast club Alfa&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/cars/nb-drifter.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;NB drifter&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;NB drifter&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/cars/tyres.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;tyres&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;tyres&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/cars/fezza.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;fezza&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;fezza&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/cars/alpine.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;alpine&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;alpine&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/cars/big-mac.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;big mac&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;big mac&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/cars/scoob.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;scoob&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;scoob&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/cars/japanuary.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;japanuary&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;japanuary&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/cars/fiat.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;fiat&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;fiat&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/cars/grubby-nissan.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;grubby nissan&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;grubby nissan&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/cars/concours.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;concours&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;concours&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/cars/triumph.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;triumph&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;triumph&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/cars/mog.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;mog&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;mog&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/cars/brute.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;brute&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;brute&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/cars/pop.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;pop&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;pop&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/cars/route-66.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;route 66&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;route 66&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/cars/cortina.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;cortina&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;cortina&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/cars/rosie.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;rosie&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;rosie&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/cars/evo.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;evo&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;evo&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/cars/rocket.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;rocket&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;rocket&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/cars/deployment.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;deployment&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;deployment&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/cars/jdm.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;jdm&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;jdm&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/cars/pop-2.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;pop&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;pop&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/cars/yellow-fire.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;yellow fire&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;yellow fire&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/cars/tent.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;tent&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;tent&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/cars/launch.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;launch&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;launch&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/cars/tingram.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;Tingram&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Tingram&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/cars/its-on.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;it&apos;s on&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;it’s on&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/cars/turbo.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;turbo&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;turbo&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/cars/torslander.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;torslander&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;torslander&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/cars/after-you.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;after you&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;after you&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/cars/action.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;action&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;action&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/cars/yuk.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;yuk&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;yuk&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/cars/he-aint-heavy.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;he ain&apos;t heavy&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;he ain’t heavy&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/cars/rivals.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;rivals&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;rivals&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/cars/watcher.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;watcher&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;watcher&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/cars/battle-mr2.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;battle mr2&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;battle mr2&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/cars/relics.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;relics&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;relics&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/cars/venom.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;venom&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;venom&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/cars/beem.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;beem&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;beem&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/cars/5.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;5&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;5&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/cars/robo.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;robo&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;robo&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/cars/spitfire.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;spitfire&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;spitfire&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/cars/safari.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;safari&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;safari&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/cars/rx150.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;rx150&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;rx150&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/cars/lap.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;lap&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;lap&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/cars/tour.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;tour&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;tour&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/cars/doom.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;doom&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;doom&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/cars/vetted.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;vetted&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;vetted&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/cars/wagon.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;wagon&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;wagon&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/cars/scimitar.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;scimitar&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;scimitar&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/cars/patina.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;patina&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;patina&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/cars/angles.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;angles&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;angles&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/cars/rx-monster.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;rx monster&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;rx monster&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/cars/minis.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;minis&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;minis&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/cars/mean-lean.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;mean lean&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;mean lean&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/cars/stanley.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;stanley&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;stanley&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/cars/rarity.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;rarity&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;rarity&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/cars/badge.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;badge&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;badge&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/cars/champ.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;champ&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;champ&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/cars/cheek.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;cheek&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;cheek&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/cars/star-time.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;star time&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;star time&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/cars/session.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;session&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;session&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/cars/doran.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;doran&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;doran&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/cars/transporter.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;transporter&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;transporter&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/cars/vip.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;vip&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;vip&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/cars/victory.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;victory&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;victory&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/cars/pressure.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;pressure&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;pressure&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/cars/chicanery.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;chicanery&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;chicanery&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/cars/saxo.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;saxo&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;saxo&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/cars/warp.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;warp&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;warp&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/cars/apex.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;apex&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;apex&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/cars/peeking.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;peeking&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;peeking&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>If it saves just one life</title>
   <link href="https://nicoboyce.com/2025/05/06/if-it-saves-just-one-life/"/>
   <updated>2025-05-06T00:00:00+01:00</updated>
   <id>https://nicoboyce.com/2025/05/06/if-it-saves-just-one-life</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;There’s talk about death and some might say I am insensitive here and if you don’t fancy that then please read something which will make you happy&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve heard this phrase come up a few times recently, I think mostly on Radio 4.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;If it saves just one life, isn’t it worth doing?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For some reason the presenter didn’t dare give the correct answer to this question:&lt;!--excerpt-end--&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;No it fucking isn’t.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here’s why.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;everyone-has-to-die&quot;&gt;Everyone has to die.&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All of us. Me, you, your accountant, your pet. If it lives, it dies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What happens when a human person dies in most societies is they establish what the cause was and they write that on a piece of paper and someone has to sign it and then that’s that done.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are a range of causes which have varying probability across demographics. If you smoke a lot of tobacco, you can reasonably expect that to be mentioned. Otherwise you pretty much get what you get.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;some-things-are-safer-than-others&quot;&gt;Some things are safer than others.&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’re super into wrestling crocodiles or motorcycle stunts or maybe you’re that guy who sneaks into building sites and climbs cranes then you probably know you’re tempting fate. If you eat a lot of kale and wear sunscreen and read fanfiction all day then there’s less danger there.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In between, there are things we deem to be necessary or important where people take a calculated risk. Firefighters. Train drivers. X-ray technicians. These people do important work which I would imagine comes with a likely reduced lifespan.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/drive.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Driver.&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Nico Boyce. Car driver. Risk taker.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are things we all do every day which are statistically more hazardous to life. Walking down stairs. Driving a car. Cooking meat. Taking a shower.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Which of those are you going to quit to marginally increase your lifespan expectation value?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;being-riskier-is-not-in-itself-sufficient-justification-to-ban-something&quot;&gt;Being riskier is not in itself sufficient justification to ban something.&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think we can all agree that knowing the risk alone isn’t enough information to end the argument. Here are some examples:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Driving is one of the most dangerous things we do day to day, but we live with that (well, mostly we live) because sometimes people and/or things need to be in other places.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Alcohol is super bad for your health, but it is enjoyable and it enables us to tolerate our loved ones and make business deals and it keeps a lot of people employed.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Medical trials can be risky for the participants but the net value of improving medical science justifies this in most people’s minds.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Oh the other hand there are things where banning has won the argument. This is usually because the risk outweighs the value generated. For example, handguns are banned in the UK. Shooting clubs can use rifles, farmers stick to shotguns, we didn’t see the value in keeping handguns following the Dunblane massacre. I would argue we should be looking to ban tobacco on a similar basis.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The two items I heard this “If it saves just one life, isn’t it worth doing?” question come up were relating to younger drivers and to internet filtering. Someone whose son died in a car accident wanted young drivers banned from taking more than one passenger. Someone whose daughter took her own life after diving into some dark corners of the web wanted a whitelisting approach to web access in the UK.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;i-do-understand-if-you-have-suffered-a-recent-bereavement-you-might-look-to-find-a-crusade&quot;&gt;I do understand if you have suffered a recent bereavement you might look to find a crusade.&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On the other hand, could we bring in people with a more objective view to temper the impulse to ban things? Perhaps this role in these conversations could have been fulfilled by the journalists of the BBC?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The conclusion I have is that we in Britain are increasingly unwilling to challenge other viewpoints. This is how you end up with people like Farage.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rational people need to stand up and say “This reasoning is not good and I think your proposal is flawed” and “Let’s see the data and consider the pros and cons” but also call it out when ridiculous arguments are being deployed with the sole intention of dividing people, such as targeting trans people or other cultures.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For a time I worried about speaking up because I was concerned about the risk of upsetting people. Now I think there’s value in being unafraid to be vocal regarding values and rationality.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m going to appropriate slogans of irrationalists. Make risk great again. You can have my car key when you pry it from my cold, dead hands.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Releasing music for drecks</title>
   <link href="https://nicoboyce.com/2025/04/22/releasing-music-for-drecks/"/>
   <updated>2025-04-22T00:00:00+01:00</updated>
   <id>https://nicoboyce.com/2025/04/22/releasing-music-for-drecks</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;some decisions and why I made them&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We have made a new album. Listen on &lt;a href=&quot;https://fightingmongooses.bandcamp.com/&quot;&gt;Bandcamp&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://tidal.com/browse/album/457375072&quot;&gt;Tidal&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://open.spotify.com/album/4xJSB3h9sIeyMfpmZZmB8n&quot;&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=OLAK5uy_nNlYcdy3bEEcBMg7ou_wpnKRIOeZRXNHk&quot;&gt;YouTube&lt;/a&gt;, or &lt;a href=&quot;https://music.apple.com/us/album/instrumental-driving-music-for-drecks/1836994336&quot;&gt;Apple Music&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/inst.webp&quot; alt=&quot;Instrumental Driving Music for Drecks&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;The Fighting Mongooses — Instrumental Driving Music for Drecks.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We’ve pretty much used all the toys on this one.&lt;!--excerpt-end--&gt; There’s some samples and some layers of ambient noise we recorded. I think I play each of the guitars on the rack at some point. There’s some upright bass and plenty of synth and also both physical and software drum machines. Most of the effects are hardware units, right down to the tape simulation and pitch shifting.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are specific moments which are nods to many of our favourite artists. There are some chords on one track which are a tip of the hat to Mark Lanegan, specifically the Scraps at Midnight record. There’s a song with a rhythm that comes from Brant Bjork and the Operators. A couple of seconds of drums are a wink at Hag Me by the Melvins. Like everything of this type, it’s a stack of things we have learned from other records. HIRS and jpegMafia and 100 Gecs and Mr Oizo and Troy Van Leeuwen’s Enemy showed us the way too.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/guits.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;Guitars.&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Guitars.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The title is a salute to the Desert Sessions but with a Cornish flavour. The photo is one I took on a driving holiday around Cumbria after thrashing the old Mazda up that hill on a Forza Horizon 4 mission, so it remembers the old podcast we did in 2020. The lettering hints at a future instalment in this series, which has more straight-up desert rock leanings via Fu Manchu.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There’s two things which were a bit more of a decision this time around. Here are those decisions and why I made them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;yes-we-are-using-a-band-name-now&quot;&gt;Yes, we are using a band name now&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Previous releases just said “Nico Boyce” on the cover. I’m okay with the name Nico Boyce because it is who I am and a name I mostly chose. On the other hand, I am building a great reputation as a Zendesk specialist (see &lt;a href=&quot;https://deltastring.com&quot;&gt;Deltastring.com&lt;/a&gt; for more on that) and I didn’t want these things colliding so much. It would be a particular problem on Youtube where &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/@deltastringdotcom&quot;&gt;we have a Deltastring channel&lt;/a&gt; now.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/nicologo.svg&quot; alt=&quot;Nico Beastie Boyce logo.&quot; width=&quot;600&quot; style=&quot;filter: hue-rotate(90deg) brightness(2);&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;My name is Nico.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There’s some talk on the Nico logo &lt;a href=&quot;/2024/05/25/where-did-the-nico-logo-design-originate/&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt; and the Deltastring logo &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.linkedin.com/posts/nicoboyce_friends-always-ask-me-about-the-deltastring-activity-7328767237085958144-eOOF?utm_source=share&amp;amp;utm_medium=member_desktop&amp;amp;rcm=ACoAAByZVBwB4YyqAQTKe01S1QkUfCQwMdIk3o4&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/ya4DuoPbVjc?si=8Qr-u-5hUtND54LS&quot; title=&quot;YouTube video player&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allow=&quot;accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share&quot; referrerpolicy=&quot;strict-origin-when-cross-origin&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Fighting Mongooses is a cool team name, as Fry says. We’re big Futurama fans. There’s not a lot more to it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Also releasing music under my name doesn’t show that it’s a team effort. Rosie shouldn’t be letting me take all the credit!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/fighting-mongooses.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;The Fighting Mongooses.&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;The Fighting Mongooses.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;no-this-isnt-on-streaming-services-yet-okay-it-is-now&quot;&gt;&lt;del&gt;No, this isn’t on streaming services (yet)&lt;/del&gt; okay it is now&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ll probably put this on most of the streaming services eventually, but I’m going to hold out as long as I can.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our &lt;a href=&quot;/music/&quot;&gt;previous music&lt;/a&gt; is on (deep breath) Spotify, Apple Music, iTunes, Instagram/Facebook, TikTok &amp;amp; other ByteDance stores, YouTube Music, Amazon, Pandora, Deezer, Tidal, iHeartRadio, Claro Música, Saavn, Anghami, KKBox, NetEase, Tencent, MediaNet, Boomplay, Adaptr, Flo, Joox, Kuack Media, Qobuz, Snapchat most of which I have never heard of.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Spotify have stopped paying smaller creators our pennies per month and almost all of these other services have never really played us. Apple and Youtube have contributed a tiny amount but not enough to make it worth the effort right now.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s not about the cash, because there isn’t any, but I feel like robbing small new artists to better fund Taylor Swift isn’t something I want to support.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This one might be a Bandcamp exclusive forever but it’s not set in stone. I’m looking at having some nice physical copies made just for vanity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;go-and-listen-to-it-and-let-me-know-what-you-think&quot;&gt;Go and listen to it and let me know what you think&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;People are really bad at supporting their friends when they create things. Give this a listen and also do let me know what you’ve created lately! I would enjoy experiencing it.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Prescott, BHC round 1</title>
   <link href="https://nicoboyce.com/wheels/2025/04/20/prescott-bhc-round-1/"/>
   <updated>2025-04-20T00:00:00+01:00</updated>
   <id>https://nicoboyce.com/wheels/2025/04/20/prescott-bhc-round-1</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/cars/prescott-25-0.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;green&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;green&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/cars/prescott-25-1.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;gold&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;gold&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/cars/prescott-25-2.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;blue&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;blue&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/cars/prescott-25-3.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;orange&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;orange&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/cars/prescott-25-4.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;red&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;red&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/cars/prescott-25-5.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;chrome&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;chrome&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/cars/prescott-25-7.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;black&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;black&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Top day out.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>On the street</title>
   <link href="https://nicoboyce.com/wheels/2025/03/10/street-cars/"/>
   <updated>2025-03-10T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
   <id>https://nicoboyce.com/wheels/2025/03/10/street-cars</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/lancia.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;Lancia&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Lancia.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/fisheye.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;Fisheye and I&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Fisheye and I.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/miatana.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;Miata NA&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Miata NA.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/chevy.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;Chevy&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Chevy.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/volvo.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;Volvo&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Volvo.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/lambo.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;Lambo&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Lambo.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/fords.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;Fords&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Fords.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/chevy-brands.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;Chevy at Brands&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Chevy at Brands.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/granada.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;Granada&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Granada.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/jeep.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;Jeep.&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Jeep.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/scoob.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Scoobs&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Scoobs.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>The F1 thing was embarrassing</title>
   <link href="https://nicoboyce.com/wheels/2025/02/15/f1-london-embarrassment/"/>
   <updated>2025-02-15T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
   <id>https://nicoboyce.com/wheels/2025/02/15/f1-london-embarrassment</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Guys the superbowl was a week ago and people were buzzing. F1 gathered all the teams to the millenium dome to unveil show cars with maybe a couple new minor sponsors.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If this is what F1 is (and it is but it’s not nice to admit that) then honestly I’m going to start trying even harder to kick the habit. I could live with the greediness if it was at least entertaining.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Dakar 25 showed the big dogs their weaknesses</title>
   <link href="https://nicoboyce.com/wheels/2025/01/25/dakar-25-big-dogs-weaknesses/"/>
   <updated>2025-01-25T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
   <id>https://nicoboyce.com/wheels/2025/01/25/dakar-25-big-dogs-weaknesses</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;In case you missed it, M-Sport turned up at Dakar with a new Ford and some not-so-quiet confidence and established big names Ekstrom and Sainz. Prodrive were positively bragging about the tech in their Dacia and brought Loeb and Al-Attiyah, the statistally greatest ever rally driver and rally-raid driver, along with Gutierrez who is up and coming and basically there in a support role with a mechanic in her co-driver’s seat.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Meanwhile, with no fanfare at all, Toyota machinery dominated the event and the eventual winner was in a privateer Hilux entry. Toyota have developed that car year after year and Team Overdrive driver Al-Rajhi is a Saudi local who navigates the Empty Quarter for fun.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Check out the Dakar channel on youtube and see how it was won.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Bike rebuild</title>
   <link href="https://nicoboyce.com/wheels/2025/01/15/bike-rebuild/"/>
   <updated>2025-01-15T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
   <id>https://nicoboyce.com/wheels/2025/01/15/bike-rebuild</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Grabbed a bargain jump bike and it needed some customisation. Popped on a super narrow and sharp looking Cinelli handlebar, a comfy GT saddle, some sick ODI x Vans grips and DMR pedals. I need to take some proper pics.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/purples.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;Purples.&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Purples.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/djbike.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;DJ.&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;DJ bike.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Italy snaps</title>
   <link href="https://nicoboyce.com/snaps/2025/01/08/italy-snaps/"/>
   <updated>2025-01-08T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
   <id>https://nicoboyce.com/snaps/2025/01/08/italy-snaps</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/vesuvius.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Vesuvius.&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Mount Vesuvius.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/scoot.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;Scooter.&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Is this the minimum viable scooter? I saw some with fewer parts but they looked dumped.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/lane.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;Narrow lane.&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;A lane, just about wide enough for two Fiat drivers to exchange paint.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/jimny.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;Jimny.&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Handsome Suzuki lurking in a hotel entrance.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Garden murder</title>
   <link href="https://nicoboyce.com/snaps/2025/01/07/garden-murder/"/>
   <updated>2025-01-07T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
   <id>https://nicoboyce.com/snaps/2025/01/07/garden-murder</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/murder.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;Garden murder.&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Garden murder.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/garden.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;Garden.&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;In the garden.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Laser tag in the woods</title>
   <link href="https://nicoboyce.com/snaps/2025/01/06/laser-tag-in-the-woods/"/>
   <updated>2025-01-06T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
   <id>https://nicoboyce.com/snaps/2025/01/06/laser-tag-in-the-woods</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/trees.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;Trees.&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Trees. Laser tag in the woods.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/mushrooms.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;Mushrooms.&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Mushrooms.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Eastney promenade</title>
   <link href="https://nicoboyce.com/snaps/2025/01/05/eastney-promenade/"/>
   <updated>2025-01-05T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
   <id>https://nicoboyce.com/snaps/2025/01/05/eastney-promenade</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/eastney.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Eastney&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Eastney.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/enter.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Enter&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Enter.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/prom.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Prom&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Prom.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/space.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Space&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Space.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Mixed snaps - January batch</title>
   <link href="https://nicoboyce.com/snaps/2025/01/04/mixed-snaps/"/>
   <updated>2025-01-04T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
   <id>https://nicoboyce.com/snaps/2025/01/04/mixed-snaps</id>
   <content type="html">
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/moon.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Moon.&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Moon.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/old.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Old.&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Old.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/trees.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Trees.&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Trees.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/robin.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Robin.&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Robin.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/bath.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Bath.&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Bath.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/cycle.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Cycle.&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Cycle.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/cremyll.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Cremyll.&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Cremyll.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/scope.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Scope.&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Scope.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/wall.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Wall.&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Wall.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/miata.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Miata.&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Miata.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/sprout.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Sprout.&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Sprout.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Bird friends</title>
   <link href="https://nicoboyce.com/snaps/2025/01/03/bird-friends/"/>
   <updated>2025-01-03T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
   <id>https://nicoboyce.com/snaps/2025/01/03/bird-friends</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/rob.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Angry robin.&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Angry robin.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/feather.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Feather&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Feather.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/prey.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Prey.&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Prey.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/caw.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Caw.&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Caw.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/gull.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Gull.&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Gull.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/twit.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Twit.&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Twit.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/peak.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Peak.&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Peak.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>In and around water</title>
   <link href="https://nicoboyce.com/snaps/2025/01/02/in-and-around-water/"/>
   <updated>2025-01-02T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
   <id>https://nicoboyce.com/snaps/2025/01/02/in-and-around-water</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/wash.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Wash.&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Wash.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/oar.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Oar.&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Oar.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/creep.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Creep.&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Creep.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/splish.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Splish.&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Splish.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Painting - silly stuff</title>
   <link href="https://nicoboyce.com/snaps/2025/01/01/painting-silly-stuff/"/>
   <updated>2025-01-01T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
   <id>https://nicoboyce.com/snaps/2025/01/01/painting-silly-stuff</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Some silly stuff&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/victor.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;Victor.&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Victor.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/frug.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Frug.&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Frug.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;fin.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Fast track</title>
   <link href="https://nicoboyce.com/wheels/2024/12/31/connor-zilisch-fast-track/"/>
   <updated>2024-12-31T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
   <id>https://nicoboyce.com/wheels/2024/12/31/connor-zilisch-fast-track</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Forget team Max or team Lando. My driver of 2024 has to be Connor Zilisch. Youtube is over there if you need to catch up with this guy.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Jag marketers are the cat's whiskers</title>
   <link href="https://nicoboyce.com/wheels/2024/12/20/jag-marketers-cats-whiskers/"/>
   <updated>2024-12-20T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
   <id>https://nicoboyce.com/wheels/2024/12/20/jag-marketers-cats-whiskers</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;All they needed to do is make one clumsy and dated video dragging them in to the 21st century and they have suddenly ceased to be the brand of golfists and top gear culture warriors. Okay so John Prescott showed you can spend your life standing up for workers and still enjoy a comfortable commute. But now they have set fire to all that in search of something interesting.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Eddie Irvine told Clive James that Jaguar was the one brand that could find that sexiness of the likes of Ferrari. Maybe at last they have got it right. Regardless, people are talking about Jag in a way that no one has since the second E Type was driven overnight from Birmingham to Geneva. I’m backing it.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Enjoy the interval</title>
   <link href="https://nicoboyce.com/2024/12/01/enjoy-the-interval/"/>
   <updated>2024-12-01T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
   <id>https://nicoboyce.com/2024/12/01/enjoy-the-interval</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;having a break from big dumb power chords&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s easy to get stuck in a rut. We can all get happy staying in our comfort zones. I’ve been struggling to write music lately just because I haven’t been trying to do anything beyond the basics.&lt;!--excerpt-end--&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My son Victor is finding his own way with music at the moment and has developed huge love for those chunky but rich sounds from British indie pop of the ’90s. We’ve had a lot of Radiohead, Blur, Elastica, Supergrass, PJ Harvey and others.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/offset.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;Twang.&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Twang.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve had Brant Bjork and the Operators on repeat in the car (since my Duna CD was found) and found some similarities in the songwriting with Victor’s playlists.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Something you’ll hear in Song 2 or in Connection by Elastica or My Ghettoblaster by Brant Bjork is using that root and fourth interval in place of the so-called powerchord of root and fifth.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is great with a Rat style distortion and an underbiased fuzz face circuit as it takes on a synth-like quality. The gated signal and square wave tone from the fuzz but with the treble filter of the Rat combine with the slight dissonance of the fourth in the 12 tone equal temperment scale to create a sound similar to the frequency modulation on an 80s analog.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Essentially I’m barring myself from the powerchord and instead aiming to write a series of songs built around showcasing different intervals. I guess time will tell if this helps break out of that rut!&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Pimped my bmx</title>
   <link href="https://nicoboyce.com/wheels/2024/11/25/pimped-my-bmx/"/>
   <updated>2024-11-25T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
   <id>https://nicoboyce.com/wheels/2024/11/25/pimped-my-bmx</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/bmx.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;Bmx.&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Bmx.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/bmx-tyre.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;Tyres.&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Tyre.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/bmx-chain.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;Chain.&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Chain.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/bikezzz.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;Park.&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Park.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Macau F3 GP</title>
   <link href="https://nicoboyce.com/wheels/2024/11/20/macau-f3-gp/"/>
   <updated>2024-11-20T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
   <id>https://nicoboyce.com/wheels/2024/11/20/macau-f3-gp</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Macau is crazy but not such a great circuit to actually race, they should reinvent it as a time trial. Nevertheless that was a mighty performance from Ugo, who nailed every restart to confirm what plenty of us have been saying for a while. This kid is the real deal. We were there at Brands Hatch when he won his first car race and now the sky is the limit. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=YYe_NXIC3H0&quot;&gt;Full feature race on the youtube&lt;/a&gt; but be prepared to fast forward…&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Mac and cheese</title>
   <link href="https://nicoboyce.com/wheels/2024/11/10/mac-and-cheese/"/>
   <updated>2024-11-10T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
   <id>https://nicoboyce.com/wheels/2024/11/10/mac-and-cheese</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;I’ve been a McLaren fan since Coulthard joined the Woking squad and as such I have always considered Ferraris to be tacky and poorly assembled and the Scuderia to be a bunch of cry babies leaning on their history to try and get preferential treatment. Ferrari are the Manchester United of F1, the idiot’s choice, the team who are more likely to license their logo for keyrings and pencil sharpeners than string a series of good performances together.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But I’ve been looking over the more affordable end of the silly cars on Autotrader lately and there’s no way I would spend money on a Mac when you put them up against the equivalent Ferrari (or even Aston or Lambo to be honest) even if I could make sense of their model lineup.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don’t know what’s a 575 or a 620 or an Artura (why does that one get a name?) and honestly I don’t care. They have all the personality (from an onlooker’s perspective) of a household appliance and I would rather walk.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Criticise this!</title>
   <link href="https://nicoboyce.com/2024/10/17/criticise-this/"/>
   <updated>2024-10-17T00:00:00+01:00</updated>
   <id>https://nicoboyce.com/2024/10/17/criticise-this</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;or perhaps Learn to Shut Up&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Everyone fancies themself as a critic. Everyone who can’t do a thing but reckons if they did do it then it would be better than you could do it. Music, film-making, art, whatever.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/noo.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;Art.&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Art. Load of old rubbish.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s the premise of half the internet now. Imdb or Yelp or Glassdoor or wherever you go. What do you think? Feel important, share your feelings.&lt;!--excerpt-end--&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Time was you could go to YouTube to learn how to do something. You could change your oil filter or wire a plug or tie a bow tie or write an application in Fortran. Now it’s wall to wall feelings and opinions. Skills are so gauche. Have a shout about something instead.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Everyone is in on it. I open the Guardian to find something to get angry at and I find that in amongst the unchallenged opinions of TERFs or crude justifications for the latest human rights violation of an ally, the editors are begging me personally to have feelings about yesterday’s celebrity death or big screen comic book adaptation. Come on, I’m busy. Ask Adrian Chiles.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Speaking of Adrian Chiles, there’s a great genre of feelings on the internet where ignorance is seen as a kind of virtuous purity. You’ve probably seen them. Person new to X picks their favourite tool for X. I don’t want the headphones someone who doesn’t like music prefers. They don’t know what they are talking about. Japanese chefs choose the best Cornish pasty. Okay great.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This phenomenon is literally the premise of Emily in Paris. Knowing nothing is a superpower, not a liability. Education is holding you back. In the land of the idiots, the person with one idea is king.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Did you even watch the new Joker film if you haven’t told someone else they are stupid for liking it or hating it or not really caring about it? Everything is “underrated” or “overrated” which is just some guy saying “I like this” or “I don’t like this” but with a bonus slice of “other people are wrong” except that it’s something pointless anyway like Call of Duty or Metallica or a Porsche.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/figures.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;Figures.&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Totally overrated probably.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let’s be honest. There’s a segment of the population who have never been told that their opinions aren’t interesting. They are the people who have never considered it but if asked would say that they are well above average at both driving and sex.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s the premise of the modern world. It’s Simon Cowell or it’s Top Gear or it’s Pitchfork or it’s Roger Ebert. Who wants to waste time creating anything real when you can come up with a witty way to put down someone else’s effort?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s the straight white male dream. The zero effort route to validation. Your hate itself is your true value. Knowing anything was always going to be a waste of time. When that guy on Reddit mentions Gamestop again you’ll be the one who gets a Lambo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Need a target for your hate? Try something that isn’t aimed at you. Laugh at the obvious deficiencies of the latest pop singer or teen drama. The lazier the better. You know what I hate? That “brat” green colour.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Go and do something. Put it out there or keep it in your bedroom. I’ll make you a deal. I’ll pretend I don’t hate it. You can shut up.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Lydden Hill snaps</title>
   <link href="https://nicoboyce.com/wheels/2024/10/15/lydden-hill-snaps/"/>
   <updated>2024-10-15T00:00:00+01:00</updated>
   <id>https://nicoboyce.com/wheels/2024/10/15/lydden-hill-snaps</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/cars/lh-pack.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;Pack.&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Pack scrap.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/cars/lh-doran.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;Doran.&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Doran.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/cars/lh-bennett.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;Bennett.&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Bennett.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/cars/lh-xcar.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;Crosscar.&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Crosscar.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/cars/lh-ford.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;Ford.&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Ford.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/cars/lh-bennett-launch.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;Launch.&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Launch.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/cars/lh-roof.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;Roof.&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Roof.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The fireworks were way better than most displays where they are the main event. Of course at Lydden it’s all about the horsepower. Top class RX cars will beat an F1 car off the line up to about 100mph. They can race on any surface and take jumps you wouldn’t believe possible. The UK is the birthplace of rallycross and it’s a great format for families and people new to motorsport. Get to Lydden Hill when you can. Also make sure you get some of that mayo from the paddock cafe when you’re there. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=l3b7TWoOxwc&quot;&gt;Watch the final on the youtube&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>E30 M25 - birthday present</title>
   <link href="https://nicoboyce.com/wheels/2024/09/01/e30-m25-birthday-present/"/>
   <updated>2024-09-01T00:00:00+01:00</updated>
   <id>https://nicoboyce.com/wheels/2024/09/01/e30-m25-birthday-present</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Got myself a birthday present.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/cars/bmw1.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;Trailer.&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Hired a trailer.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/cars/bmw2.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;Fleet.&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;At Fleet, paying our respects to Scott Mills.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/cars/bmw3.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;Home.&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;BMW at home.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/cars/bmw4.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;Victor drives.&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Victor gets comfortable.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Plenty of work needed to get it all ready for action but isn’t it a great piece of kit?&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Rethinking product pricing.</title>
   <link href="https://nicoboyce.com/2024/08/27/rethinking-product-pricing/"/>
   <updated>2024-08-27T00:00:00+01:00</updated>
   <id>https://nicoboyce.com/2024/08/27/rethinking-product-pricing</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;h3 id=&quot;or-why-traditional-saas-pricing-models-fail-and-what-im-going-to-do-about-it&quot;&gt;or Why traditional SaaS pricing models fail and what I’m going to do about it&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Selling stuff is super hard. You need people to take a punt on what you’ve made, usually by lowering the sense of risk for them. You need their feedback to improve your design and also to advocate for your item.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But then you need to make some actual cash so you hike the prices and don’t worry about letting your early advocates churn because new customers will make up for it. It’s rough&lt;!--excerpt-end--&gt; but it’s the system we’ve got.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well I’m going to do something new.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;firstly-the-product&quot;&gt;Firstly, the product&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’ll be announced soon over at &lt;a href=&quot;https://deltastring.com&quot;&gt;Deltastring.com&lt;/a&gt; but basically further to the book launch will be some software bringing additional capability to your Zendesk admin life. If you work in the Zendesk world, keep an eye out, but if you don’t, the answer is basically “business software” okay?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/zendesk-cookbook.png&quot; alt=&quot;The Zendesk Cookbook, coming soon from Nico&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;The Zendesk Cookbook, coming soon from Nico&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let’s not get bogged down in the detail there for now.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;alrighty-what-is-the-magic&quot;&gt;Alrighty what is the magic?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You’ve probably got a bunch of subscription direct debits for various things. I’ve got Tidal, Disney, Xbox, a couple others. Isn’t it exhausting each month to see which one has hiked the price this time? It doesn’t feel fair.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the world of business applications, just ten months after you finally get that purchase approved to get the tool you’ve been needing, you have to haggle again with the provider. Their costs have increased, they have new features. Great, but your budget doesn’t automatically grow! You might have to drop the thing you are now used to using. Why?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At the same time, the software company providing the tool have to remember to come back ten months after each deal is done so that they can try and squeeze more cash out of customers. A reliably consistent percentage of the time the customer will cancel and this will feel bad for everyone. Also someone has to pay for the weeks of work in haggling the new contract and all this nonsense.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;I’m not really interested in doing any of that.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here’s how it’s going to work. I’m going to put my software on sale. It’s a subscription, because it will need to be updated regularly. Paying a subscription means I can commit to doing that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s going to go on sale at a simply crazy £1 per month, then the price increases by £1 for every new subscriber. The hundredth buyer will pay £100 per month. If there’s a thousand, they will pay £1000 per month for the tool.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;As long as your subscription remains active, your price will never change.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There isn’t enough value placed on loyalty in this world. You stick with me and I’ll stick with you. I don’t want to waste time, money, energy, and goodwill by haggling with my customers every year.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The early purchasers may have to deal with a product which isn’t fully realised. It’ll be missing features they would want. It’s not going to be perfect version one. They will be the people to help me make this the best it can be. They deserve reward for that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;here-are-some-questions-and-answers&quot;&gt;Here are some questions and answers&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have a question which isn’t answered here you can &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:nico@deltastring.com&quot;&gt;email me&lt;/a&gt; and I’ll get back to you and update this page.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Won’t this eventually price out any sales?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It sure will. I’m not looking to be Amazon where everyone has an account. I’d rather support a sensible number of users than let it grow unchecked. Of course, I’m not looking to deny anyone who wants this tool regardless of cost.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What if some competitor goes crazy and buys all the early subscriptions and then cancels it and then the price is too expensive for other buyers?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m not in any way tied in to doing this. I’ll just take their money and then reset the pricing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Could someone skip a month and keep the same pricing?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Nope, every price is a one time deal. I need reliable and predictable income! I have a family.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Will you be doing free trials? This sounds interesting but we’d need a month to evaluate.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;No. You can buy a month. If you can’t buy a month to try it out then you were never going to be able to raise the budget to pay for the tool in the first place. Free trials are bad for everyone. Plus, you get the price earlier, therefore cheaper.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;enough-already-show-me-the-thing&quot;&gt;Enough already, show me the thing&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Be patient!&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Meanwhile, in ancient Rome</title>
   <link href="https://nicoboyce.com/2024/08/18/meanwhile-in-ancient-rome/"/>
   <updated>2024-08-18T00:00:00+01:00</updated>
   <id>https://nicoboyce.com/2024/08/18/meanwhile-in-ancient-rome</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;We went to Pompeii and it was a lot.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/pompeii.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;Pompeii.&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Pompeii and Vesuvius&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My partner and I are both reformed history geeks. We’re not so occupied with the past these days but I think either of us would have said that we were pretty knowledgable on Pompeii for people who hadn’t been there in person. We’d know to look in the hortus&lt;!--excerpt-end--&gt; if we couldn’t find Caecilius.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Pompeii is properly crazy though.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;pompeii-is-super-big&quot;&gt;Pompeii is super big&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don’t think we were ready for the scale of the area you can walk around. It’s probably the size of your local small town, except that when you are there you probably don’t look in everyone’s house, each shop, the churches, whatever they have there. With Pompeii, you do explore in that way so it is a big old site.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This means it breaks through the buffers in your head saying it’s an open air museum or recreation or something. It just is a Roman town where people were busy doing their Roman stuff.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;life-in-the-area-basically-hasnt-changed&quot;&gt;Life in the area basically hasn’t changed&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are deep gashes in the cobbles from where cart wheels repeatedly dug in to the surface as traders rushed around. Get a taxi at the local airport and see how that ride goes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Excavations have revealed seventy fast food joints. Big stone counters with clay pots of local fish and veg and such. Head into Naples and walk along Via Foria and see how far you can get without buying a snack.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Romans loved drawing dicks everywhere. Dicks are funny and stupid. This is still true today.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;the-whole-volcano-thing&quot;&gt;The whole volcano thing&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Pompeii isn’t as close to Vesuvius as I thought. Really a lot of people live much closer now, and the same was true in AD79. It’s big and imposing but probably if you live there you don’t stare at it so much.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/vesuvius.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Vesuvius.&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;That there Vesuvius&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s pretty hefty though. The crater is bigger than the quarry we used to sneak into back in Cornwall. Also it starts at basically the sea, so you get the full effect of the height. If you go to Scafell then you’re probably already starting most of the way up.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Prescott hillclimb - classic day out</title>
   <link href="https://nicoboyce.com/wheels/2024/08/15/prescott-bhc-classic/"/>
   <updated>2024-08-15T00:00:00+01:00</updated>
   <id>https://nicoboyce.com/wheels/2024/08/15/prescott-bhc-classic</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;We went to Prescott (which is the Bugatti Owners Club place in Gloucestershire) for the British Hillclimb Championship which is all on the youtube if you want to see it in a video format &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=rn7df2xiabM&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We looked like this&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/us.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;Us.&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;This is us.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here are some of the cars:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/cars/prescott-abarth.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;Abarth.&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/cars/prescott-bugatti.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;Bugatti.&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/cars/prescott-hill.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;The hill.&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/cars/prescott-1.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;Prescott.&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/cars/prescott-2.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;Prescott again.&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/cars/prescott-cigar.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;Cigar.&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/cars/prescott-frogeye.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;Frogeye.&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/cars/prescott-glow.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;Glow.&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/cars/prescott-hill.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;Hill.&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/cars/prescott-legend.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;Legend.&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/cars/prescott-mitsubishi.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;Mitsubishi.&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/cars/prescott-paddock.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;Paddock.&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/cars/prescott-porsche.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;Porsche.&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/cars/prescott-radical.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;Radical.&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/cars/prescott-rapid.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;Rapid.&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/cars/prescott-semicircle.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;Semi-circle.&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/cars/prescott-seven.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;Seven.&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/cars/prescott-subarus.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;Subarus.&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/cars/prescott-traction.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;Traction.&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Can you spot which were taken with the Nikon D3300 and which were taken with the Fujifilm X-H2?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was one of the best motorsport events I’ve been to, a really great day out. Looking forward to next year.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Naples car culture</title>
   <link href="https://nicoboyce.com/wheels/2024/07/20/naples-car-culture/"/>
   <updated>2024-07-20T00:00:00+01:00</updated>
   <id>https://nicoboyce.com/wheels/2024/07/20/naples-car-culture</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Naples had a weird car thing going on. I loved seeing the Lancia and Dacia stuff that never made it to the UK and the splutter of air cooled Fiats is pleasing to me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/cars/126.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;Fiat.&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;In Naples you leave your door open and your handbrake off. If someone is determined to enter or move your car, just let them.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve got to get me something like this.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/cars/cargrid1.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;Cars.&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/cars/cargrid2.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;Cars.&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/cars/cargrid3.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;Cars.&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/cars/cargrid4.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;More cars.&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Now we know.</title>
   <link href="https://nicoboyce.com/2024/07/07/now-now-now/"/>
   <updated>2024-07-07T00:00:00+01:00</updated>
   <id>https://nicoboyce.com/2024/07/07/now-now-now</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;I’ve added a now page to the site. If you have a site a bit like this, maybe you should give it a go too?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The now page is there to be a quick summary of what I’m up to, what I would explain to a friend I hadn’t caught up with in a while. It’s different to a social media page, where you might share things on a more minute level, or to a blog where each post would have its own narrow scope. The now page has its own brief.&lt;!--excerpt-end--&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;where-does-it-come-from&quot;&gt;Where does it come from?&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well all that is explained &lt;a href=&quot;https://nownownow.com/about&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt; well enough that I shouldn’t be rewriting it. I’m glad to see that personal sites still exist and that the conventions for those are still evolving.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;what-will-you-be-putting-there&quot;&gt;What will you be putting there?&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well, I’m not sure right now but I guess it’ll cover my making and doing. It’ll also serve to help me keep track of what I’m halfway through!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/yellow.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;Nico Beastie Boyce.&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;BMXing has kept me pretty busy lately.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The page is &lt;a href=&quot;/now/&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt; and I hope over time it has some value to me and to you.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>In Bloom (or maybe Come As You Are)</title>
   <link href="https://nicoboyce.com/2024/05/28/in-bloom-or-come-as-you-are/"/>
   <updated>2024-05-28T00:00:00+01:00</updated>
   <id>https://nicoboyce.com/2024/05/28/in-bloom-or-come-as-you-are</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;I am not much of a gardener. Sometimes I will get out there and do some hacking and chopping and digging and pruning, but only for theraputic reasons. It feels nice to me when I can impress my will upon the hectic growth.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Nevertheless if I just left it to do what it wanted then the landlord and neighbours would be bothered by this. I feel like the garden and I have this unstable equilibrium where we gently push against each other until a reaction is provoked.&lt;!--excerpt-end--&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;my-ideal-garden&quot;&gt;My ideal garden&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am no Capability Brown, as you are gathering. For me the ideal garden has sufficient space for me to do my things but also is low effort, in keeping with the location, encouraging to the local animals. Here we have kites, a kestral, barn and tawny owls, squirrels, muntjac and roe deer. Plenty of hares and rabbits come by, as well as the odd weasel or stoat (I don’t know the differences) and really a lot of butterflies and birds.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/beetle.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;A beetle in the garden.&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;A beetle in the garden.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s also nice to have something useful in the garden. I do wish we had a bay tree, but we’re well equipped for chives and some other basic edible leaves. There’s an apple tree too, so we have nice cox apples annually.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/flower1.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;A flower.&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;A flower. I don’t really know about flowers.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A grassy lawn framed by neat beds is really the antithesis of fun in my mind. While it is useful to have some green space for outdoor activities, I like a much more diverse setting.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;the-garden-we-have&quot;&gt;The garden we have&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Since this is a temporary home for us, with maybe another six months or year before we vacate, I’ve not made a huge effort to transform the space. There are plenty of plants that I would rip straight out if I knew I would be here in the summer of 2025, but as it stands I can live with them for now.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/flower2.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;Another flower.&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Another flower. These are all straight-off-the-camera crops.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Apparently these roses are ornamental types grafted onto a hardier rose variety. This, I am told, means you get a fancy flower but without all the care needed. This makes sense since I have provided zero care.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some of these plants seem like odd decisions. There’s a row of daffodils that came up along a path that leads to an old shed. They lasted a few days and sure made looking for the strimmer seem luxurious.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/flower3.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;Also a flower.&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;I don’t know what this is, but it looks like the kind of flower they print on a dress in M&amp;amp;S.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All this is of course just an excuse to show you some photos I took. Do you like flowers? I don’t know whether it is worth trying to incorporate their shapes and colours into my art, which can be somewhat geometric.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am a fan of the artwork of Takeshi Kitano as showcased in the Hana-Bi film where specific flowers were reimagined. They are also interesting from the perspective of being the sex organs of the plant. My art primarily examines the role of technology in society, so I don’t know where this fits. Perhaps some day gardening will lead to inspiration.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/flower4.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;One last flower.&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;One last flower. I don’t encourage people to visit, so these are mostly just for me.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now to go and prune these blooms.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Applying logic and maths in Monte Carlo. When to pit at the Monaco Grand Prix?</title>
   <link href="https://nicoboyce.com/wheels/2024/05/26/maths-in-monte-carlo-monaco-grand-prix/"/>
   <updated>2024-05-26T00:00:00+01:00</updated>
   <id>https://nicoboyce.com/wheels/2024/05/26/maths-in-monte-carlo-monaco-grand-prix</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Formula One is a sport made almost entirely of maths, but the commentators rarely use the full toolkit of logic while talking viewers through the races. Maybe they think it won’t be exciting to examine the competition in this way? Regardless, let’s throw some logic at today’s grand prix and see what bounces back.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/redbull.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;Max Verstappen&apos;s Red Bull car&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Max Verstappen’s Red Bull car, photo from my own archive.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;If you haven’t seen the 2024 Monaco Grand Prix but you’re planning to catch up, do that and then come back to this article.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;!--excerpt-end--&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;background-to-the-2024-monaco-grand-prix&quot;&gt;Background to the 2024 Monaco Grand Prix&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As tradition dictates, it’s the last Sunday in May and I’ve just watched the Monaco Grand Prix and I’m having a bite before the Indy 500, but mostly I’m chewing over the difference between the expectations of the Sky F1 commentators and the decisions of the team strategists.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;No team is anywhere near challenging Max Verstappen and Red Bull in the points, but Monaco is a very historic race and one where a lot of important sponsorship deals are done. A win at Monaco is particularly prized by the more established teams, Ferrari and McLaren.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Monaco is a circuit where it is notoriously difficult to overtake, in fact virtually impossible in 2024. Ferrari and their polesitter driver Leclerc are still seeking redemption for the &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/2021_Monaco_Grand_Prix&quot;&gt;2021 race&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;what-was-happening&quot;&gt;What was happening?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let’s jump to around halfway through the race. Here was the order (of the top seven, cars behind these are not relevant to this article)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Charles Leclerc, Ferrari&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Oscar Piastri, McLaren&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Carlos Sainz Jr, Ferrari&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Lando Norris, McLaren&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;George Russell, Mercedes&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Max Verstappen, Red Bull&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Lewis Hamilton, Mercedes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Current F1 rules require each car to use two different types of tyre in a dry race. The first four of these started on the medium tyre and the other three took the hard tyre for the start, but a first lap incident meant that they were all able to change their tyres. Therefore they all took the opposite choice and none have any mandatory pit stops for the remainder of the race. The Ferrari and McLaren cars are now on the durable but slower hard tyres and the Mercedes and Red Bull cars are on the grippier medium tyres.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can imagine that Russell, Verstappen, and Hamilton are all now becoming concerned about the remaining lifespan of their tyres, while those ahead are more worried that they could be vulnerable to a car on quicker rubber in the event of a caution period.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Leclerc was trying to slow the pace of the race for the frontrunners. George Russell was also focusing on extending the life of his tyres through keeping his corner speeds down. A substantial gap had developed behind Lewis Hamilton.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;lewis-stops-does-max&quot;&gt;Lewis stops, does Max?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lewis Hamilton was called to the pits and would change to hard tyres, I think the same set that he had used for the first lap. There was a 45 second gap behind, so there was no risk of losing a position.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Max Verstappen followed this with a stop on the next lap. He emerged ahead of Lewis Hamilton but within sight of the Mercedes driver. Lewis felt that he should have been told that there could be an opportunity to pass Max, saying so over the team radio, and the Sky commentators agreed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/f1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Benetton F1 car&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Benetton F1 car, a B190 I think. I snapped this at the Thruxton Historic. I didn’t have any more relevant photos I owned to hand.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Maths tells us that this is just not the case though. Lewis Hamilton had a a small gap between himself and Max before the stops, about four seconds, which would have been too much to overcome in one lap without teammate George Russell deliberately slowing Max Verstappen on the lap between.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But that doesn’t matter, because remember Max Verstappen (and indeed all of the drivers) did not need to stop. If Lewis Hamilton managed a fast enough lap time (or Max Verstappen was sufficiently slowed) then the Red Bull team would just have decided to stay on track and make the best of the tyres Max had. Lewis taking new tyres was a no-brainer because there was no substantial risk of losing the position either way, also there was no likely scenario of improving under normal circumstances, so they might as well make their life easier en route to that 7th place finish.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The strategy team at Red Bull Racing had made the same calculation. There was no probable route to an improved position, but no likely consequence for taking new tyres at this point, so they did so.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sorry Lewis Hamilton, sorry Sky F1, but in this case you were incorrect.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;did-lewis-cause-problems-for-george&quot;&gt;Did Lewis cause problems for George?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A lap later, George Russell did not stop and take new tyres. Max Verstappen was a lot faster on his new tyres and had been very close to George beforehand. He quickly reduced the deficit to the extent that George Russell did not have the free pit stop option. I shouted at the television that this proved my point, but David Croft and Martin Brundle couldn’t hear me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Verstappen and Hamilton continued to put decent times in (at least compared to the rest of the field) and soon Russell was coming under some pressure from Max Verstappen. It was starting to look like the actions of Hamilton’s crew had adversely affected his teammate, who would now have to continue on the worn-out medium tyres until the chequered flag while the World Champion looks for an opportunity to muscle through.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Could Mercedes have planned for this? There were two options. Either they needed to prevent the Verstappen pit stop or they needed to enable one for George Russell.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The way to prevent Max having the option of a stop was to ensure the space between George and Lewis was minimised at all times. Red Bull are fast and consistent with tyre changes but they aren’t looking to risk throwing away points for no reason. Lewis needed to speed up on his in and out laps and George needed to hold up Max as far as possible on those same two laps.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is definitely plausible that Lewis Hamilton could have pushed harder (he did say so!) and I’m sure George Russell could have gone slower without risking a rash move from Max Verstappen. Therefore Lewis actually should have been told to push (perhaps even telling him there was a chance to beat Max, even though there was not) just to protect his teammate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In any case, it made no difference to the eventual result.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To enable a stop for George Russell, he would have needed to gain time relative to Max Verstappen over the three laps in question. If the timing showed 21-22 seconds gap by the time George Russell reached the Piscine (swimming pool) section on the lap following Max Verstappen’s stop then that would have done the job. This was never likely to be the case unless Red Bull made a mistake with the tyre change, with no way for Mercedes to show Verstappen.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;okay-so-what-about-the-lead-four&quot;&gt;Okay so what about the lead four?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;It may at this point in the article be evident that the Indy 500 has been delayed and the curry hasn’t yet arrived and I had more time than I expected to write this article.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The front four were pretty much nose to tail for lap after lap. On the Sky coverage, ex racers Anthony Davidson and Martin Brundle agreed that the Ferrari and McLaren teams would need to make pitstops themselves. This made no sense, and I’m surprised that everyone couldn’t see that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Remember that there’s really no way to pass a racer at Monaco if they don’t make a major error. In 2018, Daniel Ricciardo won the Monaco Grand Prix despite the failure of his engine’s hybrid system and a faltering gearbox with two shattered cogs. I realise this must sound insane to people who don’t watch F1. Be assured that you are completely right.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lando Norris, in fourth, would have nothing to gain by taking fresh tyres unless he knew in advance that the cars ahead of him would also stop. He would also need a gap of at least 21 seconds behind him to George Russell to be assured of retaining his position. I don’t think he ever quite had sufficient gap and there was no way Ferrari would surrender track position even if they were down to the rims.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/f1s.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;Some F1 cars at Thruxton&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;This is not how Monaco went today.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If the gap had developed then it seems reasonable to assume that McLaren would take the precaution of mounting fresh Pirellis on the car of Norris. This would not have triggered the same chain reaction we saw with Verstappen responding to Hamilton, because the four leaders were always so close together and new tyres would have been faster. Even if Norris built the space behind to take fresh tyres, Sainz would always have stayed out to maintain track position. There was never a chance of a positive outcome.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Even if the Norris crew could see the future and predict a safety car (though there wasn’t one) then Ferrari could always beat McLaren by just doing nothing and staying ahead. In fact, even the Singapore 2008 scenario wasn’t possible today.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Brundle and Davidson focused on the fact that stopping earlier would benefit Norris if all of the lead pack pitted (or at least one of the Ferraris) but this required McLaren to be sure that Ferrari would decide to stop for tyres. Instead, it was obvious that they would not decide to do that. The proposed strategy only wins in the scenario where you already know your opponent’s next move.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;alright-so-what-is-your-point&quot;&gt;Alright, so what is your point?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don’t think Davidson and Brundle have any interest in misleading viewers, in trying to create tension where there really isn’t any. Martin Brundle has always been a straight-shooter as a broadcaster. He had for years warned about the specific danger of the scenario which led to the death of Jules Bianchi, for example. Davidson also has nothing to gain from any kind of chicanery.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bernie Collins has been a part of the Sky team at some races recently. Bernie is a strategy engineer with F1 experience, who brings a good dose of sense to the broadcast. I definitely notice the difference when she isn’t available to bring her insights.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Monaco is always an impressive spectacle. There’s nowhere else you can see cars this fast competing around such tight streets. Don’t tune in to the Monaco Grand Prix in future years expecting to see plenty of wheel to wheel action and don’t assume that the commentators know what they are talking about!&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Where did the Nico logo design originate?</title>
   <link href="https://nicoboyce.com/2024/05/25/where-did-the-nico-logo-design-originate/"/>
   <updated>2024-05-25T00:00:00+01:00</updated>
   <id>https://nicoboyce.com/2024/05/25/where-did-the-nico-logo-design-originate</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;I put together a logo of my name soon after I chose my name itself. It looks like this:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/nicologo.svg&quot; alt=&quot;Nico Beastie Boyce logo.&quot; width=&quot;600&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;This is my logo thing.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is how I put it together.&lt;!--excerpt-end--&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;nico-rosberg&quot;&gt;Nico Rosberg&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lewis Hamilton and Nico Rosberg made huge waves en route to Formula One and were very exciting junior drivers at the point where I was first watching the lower rungs of the single-seater ladder. Rosberg was one of the influences on my choice of name and so I did look to him for ideas for a design. I wanted to reference my appreciation for his achievements but with an individual twist.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can see Nico Rosberg’s logo on the cockpit of this Airbus, replicating his helmet design. The N and I are not connected, and the O has a break in it mirroring the C, but the proportions and concept are similar.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/nicorosberg.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Nico Rosberg helmet design on an Airbus&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Nico Rosberg’s Williams era helmet design, on an Airbus.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This wasn’t actually the first thing I considered for my own design, but it’s the first thing F1 fans will spot.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;sony-vaio&quot;&gt;Sony Vaio&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I primarily took inspiration from the Sony Vaio logo. There are plenty of good articles discussing this design, such as &lt;a href=&quot;https://imjustcreative.com/the-sony-vaio-logo/2022/10/21&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;. Essentially, consider the VA as a waveform representing analogue signals and the IO representing binary code and therefore digital signals.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/Sony_VAIO_P.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;VAIO P series, Yoggy from Yokohama, Kanagawa, Japan, CC BY 2.0&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;VAIO P series, Yoggy from Yokohama, Kanagawa, Japan, CC BY 2.0&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This resonated with my own background, as a one-time photonics student turned musician, or as an artist and engineer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;the-geometry&quot;&gt;The geometry&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I created the original sketch in a maths education package called Cabri-Géomètre. The O and C were simply overlapping circles (by the full width of the character at the intersection) with the gap in the C character the circumference length of the difference in radius between the inner and outer edges.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The width of the N was four times the width of each stroke, i.e. the white space between left and right leg of the N was double the stroke. Originally the I was the same distance on from there (and therefore the curve linking the N and I matched the top of the N) but this looked super weird so I halved it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Everything looked a bit precise and weird, so I took a screenshot at low resolution, upped the contrast, smoothed the resulting image, then used an online SVG converter. Then there’s a few little tweaks directly in the resulting XML, notably the radius of the I dot circle (it is a tad larger) and the shape of the top end of the C.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;explanation&quot;&gt;Explanation&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The first two characters, N and I, are linked to create a waveform, representitive of analogue audio signals. The dotted i form represents a photon, and so draws the link to photonics and optics and the wider science of light and colour. Combined, they illustrate the particle-wave duality and also the dual aspects of my output.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My work combines science, software, engineering, maths, and code, but also the subjective nature of creation, the necessarily analogue processes of performing in sound and colour. After that there is the return to digital and the metaphorical waveform collapse as the sensor resolves the information into bits and bytes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The second characters continue the theme, as the C and O combine to make an infinity symbol which is broken. Infinity represents my background in science and maths once again but also the scope of the art world. The shape itself is reminiscent of race circuits and loci showing the mechanical motion of wheels.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 

</feed>
