<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.3.4">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://nicoboyce.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="https://nicoboyce.com/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2026-02-01T23:26:12+00:00</updated><id>https://nicoboyce.com/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Nico Boyce</title><subtitle>Person doing human things</subtitle><author><name>Nico Beastie Boyce</name></author><entry><title type="html">Days, in 35mm slices</title><link href="https://nicoboyce.com/snaps/2026/01/15/days-in-35mm-slices/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Days, in 35mm slices" /><published>2026-01-15T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2026-01-15T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://nicoboyce.com/snaps/2026/01/15/days-in-35mm-slices</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://nicoboyce.com/snaps/2026/01/15/days-in-35mm-slices/"><![CDATA[<p>I’m obviously not quite busy enough so why not revisit the problems of the past to make hobbies even more expensive and time consuming?</p>

<p>I’ve been using this pretty much exclusively for the last couple of months. It’s chunky and clunky and old. It’s opinionated about the way things should be done. It can be a bit frustrating and temperamental. It’s hard to know why I feel something for this tool.</p>

<p><img src="/public/img/nikon-f601.jpg" alt="Nikon." />
<em>Nikon F-601.</em></p>

<p>The camera gear situation is getting a bit silly here lately. I have sold some lenses and the Fuji X-H2 but it’s definitely excessive nevertheless. Here is some of the stuff.</p>

<p><img src="/public/img/cameras.jpeg" alt="Cameras." />
<em>Cameras.</em></p>

<p>Anyway more interesting probably is what’s coming out of the camera. I’ve used it for a range of photography and with a mix of Fuji and Kodak film. I’m getting everything developed by <a href="https://www.thefilmsafe.co.uk/?nicoboycedotcom">The Film Safe</a> who are just delightful. Which are your favourite shots?</p>

<p><img src="/public/img/35mm/bhtruck.jpg" alt="BH Truck." />
<em>BH Truck.</em></p>

<p><img src="/public/img/35mm/closed.jpeg" alt="Closed." />
<em>Closed.</em></p>

<p><img src="/public/img/35mm/crow.jpg" alt="Crow." />
<em>Crow.</em></p>

<p><img src="/public/img/35mm/dawlish.jpg" alt="Dawlish." />
<em>Dawlish.</em></p>

<p><img src="/public/img/35mm/portsdown.jpg" alt="Portsdown." />
<em>Portsdown.</em></p>

<p><img src="/public/img/35mm/splash.jpeg" alt="Splash." />
<em>Splash.</em></p>

<p><img src="/public/img/35mm/track.jpeg" alt="Track." />
<em>Track.</em></p>]]></content><author><name>Nico Beastie Boyce</name></author><category term="snaps" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’m obviously not quite busy enough so why not revisit the problems of the past to make hobbies even more expensive and time consuming? I’ve been using this pretty much exclusively for the last couple of months. It’s chunky and clunky and old. It’s opinionated about the way things should be done. It can be a bit frustrating and temperamental. It’s hard to know why I feel something for this tool. Nikon F-601. The camera gear situation is getting a bit silly here lately. I have sold some lenses and the Fuji X-H2 but it’s definitely excessive nevertheless. Here is some of the stuff. Cameras. Anyway more interesting probably is what’s coming out of the camera. I’ve used it for a range of photography and with a mix of Fuji and Kodak film. I’m getting everything developed by The Film Safe who are just delightful. Which are your favourite shots? BH Truck. Closed. Crow. Dawlish. Portsdown. Splash. Track.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Yes, I have been rollerblading a lot</title><link href="https://nicoboyce.com/2026/01/06/rolling/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Yes, I have been rollerblading a lot" /><published>2026-01-06T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2026-01-06T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://nicoboyce.com/2026/01/06/rolling</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://nicoboyce.com/2026/01/06/rolling/"><![CDATA[<p><em>now I’m going to talk about it</em></p>

<p>Rollerblading is a polarising thing to do. I can’t think of many other hobbies which draw so much comment from passers-by. If you like to keep a low profile, if you like to avoid talking to strangers, don’t do rollerblading.</p>

<p><img src="/public/img/solent.jpg" alt="By the sea." />
<em>By the sea.</em></p>

<p>I used to love rolling around as a kid. It was interrupted by injuries<!--excerpt-end--> (I broke my arm twice when I was nine) and other interests came along at 12. We’re talking Magic the Gathering, Quake 3, Terry Pratchett. Oh also I learned to ride a bike about that time. Before 12 though, there were about four years where being outside meant being on tiny wheels.</p>

<p>By the end I was pretty good! I could skate backwards pretty much as quick as forwards, I got picked for a roller hockey team, I had plenty of good times on my blades. It’s okay to grow up.</p>

<h2 id="now-it-turns-out-being-grown-isnt-all-great">Now it turns out being grown isn’t all great</h2>

<p>I think I’m doing pretty well at being an adult. I do a job I enjoy and it funds doing plenty of fun stuff. I’ve got nice adult toys (no not in that sense, you sleaze) like <a href="https://nicoboyce.com/essays/2025/04/22/releasing-music-for-drecks/">guitars</a> and <a href="https://nicoboyce.com/gear/">camping kit</a> and <a href="https://nicoboyce.com/snaps/">photography</a> gear and <a href="https://nicoboyce.com/wheels/2024/09/01/e30-m25-birthday-present/">the BMW</a>. On the other hand, I’m only getting older! No amount of sim racing gear or guitar pedals will slow that.</p>

<p>So why not treat myself and take up skating again, with the kind of set-up I would have loved as a kid?</p>

<p><strong>There’s no reason, the question was rhetorical</strong></p>

<p>So I grabbed some from a charity shop (which happened to be the same boots as the ones I had as a kid! Obviously a tad bigger now) but it turns out I’m a bit more sophisticated (and heavy) than I was at that age and I needed something better.</p>

<p>Here’s what I’m rolling on lately:</p>

<p><img src="/public/img/skates.jpg" alt="Skates." />
<em>Skates.</em></p>

<p>They are a pretty great ride!</p>

<h2 id="this-is-all-fun-and-games-but-im-only-here-for-the-tech-specs">This is all fun and games but I’m only here for the tech specs</h2>

<p>I’m rolling on <strong>Roces M12 UFS Lo</strong> with some modifications.</p>

<p>Roces have apparently existed since 1952. I wasn’t around then but I will take their word for it. The M12 boot was launched in 1996, so it was the latest and greatest when I was starting! I would have loved some then. I love these now instead!</p>

<p>UFS is the Universal Frame System. Yes, the rollerskate companies agreed on some basic compatibility long before anyone even dared to ask Apple to make any effort to co-operate with other PC manufacturers. It just specifies a couple of mount points on the sole and the dimensions of the frame, which is the piece the wheels are mounted in.</p>

<p>Lo on the Roces means that the cuff and the liner don’t go so high up your calf at the back. This is a preference thing. The liner in these boots is a basic one from Loco Skates.</p>

<p>The stock Roces frame is probably great if you’re under 40kg but I had two issues with it. The middle wheels are “antirocker” types, which means they are actually just spacers really. They don’t roll and don’t have bearings in them. Again, this is probably fine for kids and people who are very serious about rollerblading but I’m a busy dad who eats too many biscuits.</p>

<p>Additionally, the stock frame is quite flexible. I think it’s made of nylon and I didn’t have much confidence on it.</p>

<h3 id="a-word-on-configurations">A word on configurations</h3>

<p>Antirocker wheels are called that because your first and fourth wheel on each boot wear down much quicker and so if you have equal wheels (flat configuration) then you end up with a bit of a rocking sensation as your foot seesaws over the middle wheels. This feels bad, so antirocker exists.</p>

<p><img src="/public/img/roces.jpg" alt="Antirocker." />
<em>Antirocker.</em></p>

<p>If you want a flat setup (i.e. four equal wheels) then you need to periodically swap the positions of your wheels around to prevent it becoming a rocker.</p>

<p>You can also get a “freestyle” configuration where you just take out the middle wheels and so have two wheels on each boot. This is lighter but you lose grip on tight turns or hard stops.</p>

<p>Some people do ride a rocker setup apparently. Weirdos.</p>

<h3 id="modifications">Modifications</h3>

<p>I added a foam insole of some sort to help my weird feet. Plastic boots need plenty of padding whoever you are though.</p>

<p>The laces are now these really classy yellow ones. They match…all of my things. A great style upgrade.</p>

<p><img src="/public/img/roces2.jpg" alt="Laces." />
<em>Laces.</em></p>

<p>The stock wheels (though not the inside wheels remember) were Revolver branded. I think they are 64mm and 88a hardness rated. They have a very round profile. It felt to me like I was on stilts and there wasn’t much rubber on the road. I switched them for some Iqon wheels which were 55mm 85a and have a square profile, so a large contact patch. These are indoor wheels really, so they have super high rolling resistance and you feel every molecule of imperfection in the road.</p>

<p>I’ve now swapped the frames for 50-50 Prime frames. Rosie got me these for a present and I am very happy with them. Each boot is a little heavier but the frame has an aluminium structure and feels absolutely rock solid. It has given me the confidence to put the Revolver wheels on the front and back and the Iqon wheels in the middle positions, which honestly feels so great!</p>

<p><img src="/public/img/skating.jpeg" alt="Skating time." />
<em>Skating time.</em></p>

<p>I’m rolling on Bones bearings and they are okay but honestly I hoped for more from them. Fancy ABEC 9 bearings on the outside wheels at least would be the next thing to do.</p>

<p>In a straight line, there’s much less rolling resistance so it is less difficult to get moving. On a turn, the middle wheels with their softer rubber and flatter profile really help bite into the tarmac and turn me around.</p>

<h2 id="so-what">So what?</h2>

<p>Hey, this is my website and I’ll talk about rollerskating if I want to. And if that makes you want to throw things at me, well I’m still laughing because I’ve got this classy helmet!</p>

<p><img src="/public/img/lid.jpg" alt="Helmet." />
<em>Helmet.</em></p>]]></content><author><name>Nico Beastie Boyce</name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[now I’m going to talk about it Rollerblading is a polarising thing to do. I can’t think of many other hobbies which draw so much comment from passers-by. If you like to keep a low profile, if you like to avoid talking to strangers, don’t do rollerblading. By the sea. I used to love rolling around as a kid. It was interrupted by injuries]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">2025 is over</title><link href="https://nicoboyce.com/2025/12/31/it-is-over/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="2025 is over" /><published>2025-12-31T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2025-12-31T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://nicoboyce.com/2025/12/31/it-is-over</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://nicoboyce.com/2025/12/31/it-is-over/"><![CDATA[<p><em>wow that was a time wasn’t it</em></p>

<p>So yes today is the LAST DAY OF THE YEAR and so here are some thoughts which I have had on various topics. Do you agree? Do you disagree? That’s okay!</p>

<h2 id="music-sounds-etc">Music, sounds, etc</h2>

<p>I guess for a lot of people 2025 was about waiting in virtual queues hoping to get tickets to big stadium shows from lowest common denominator pop acts. I’m not mad at you if you are in to that, I’m just disappointed and let’s not speak about it further.</p>

<p>We saw some really great stuff. Have A Nice Life. Divide And Dissolve. Earth. The Beta Band! High On Fire (plus incredible supports including Castle Rat) and I’m sure I’m forgetting so many excellent other bands. Queens of the Stone Age a couple of times.</p>

<p>I’ve heard people say don’t meet your heroes. They need to choose their heroes better. I’ve met pretty much all of my musical idols and they were almost all absolutely lovely.</p>

<p><img src="/public/img/earth.jpg" alt="Earth." />
<em>Dylan Carlson of Earth.</em></p>

<h3 id="how-about-new-music">How about new music?</h3>

<p>So 2025 was a year where artists whose work I had been enjoying over the last few years released records which made me go “oh okay, that’s a shame.”</p>

<p>Here are some of those:</p>

<ul>
  <li>Earl Sweatshirt</li>
  <li>Simz</li>
  <li>Ikonika</li>
  <li>FKA Twigs</li>
  <li>JPEGMAFIA</li>
  <li>Divide And Dissolve</li>
  <li>Princess Nokia</li>
  <li>Yaya Bey</li>
  <li>Masters of Reality</li>
</ul>

<p>None of these were bad! They were all fine but just not super great.</p>

<p>Anyone who had Eusexua on their best-of lists honestly probably just hasn’t recently revisited the best stuff Madonna and Bjork did in the 1990s.</p>

<p>While collating this list I made a note that I need to put some more time in to the newest Clipping and Kae Tempest records.</p>

<p>My favourite new record this year was PinkPanteress mixtape Fancy That and my favourite new song of the year was Music by Underscores and nothing else really came close to those choices for me.</p>

<p>Finally I’ve got to say “go and listen to Esdeekid” if you’re not yet in on that thing.</p>

<h3 id="live-highlights">Live highlights?</h3>

<p>My favourite performance I got to experience this year is a bit more tough. I’m going to pick individual songs from shows, why not.</p>

<p>The Bees Made Honey in the Lion’s Skull by Earth at the Electric Ballroom was like the whole world was revolving around the incredible patience of drummer Adrienne. Teased out over what felt like hours, this rendition of this track was so powerful I don’t know how we made it home afterwards.</p>

<p>Queens of the Stone Age, Long Slow Goodbye at the Royal Albert Hall. I didn’t have Josh Homme waving a hatchett around and Matt Berry pulling out all the stops on the monstrous RAH organ on my bingo card for the year.</p>

<p>The Beta Band, Dry the Rain. This was at the Roundhouse. It felt like a strange moment in my life. The two decades since their last shows, one of the first proper gigs I made it to, all of that seemed forgiven in that moment.</p>

<h2 id="tv-cinema-audiovisual-media">TV, cinema, audiovisual media</h2>

<p>I am always saying I don’t feel like film is a great way to tell a story. Nothing in 2025 has changed my view on that. I have really struggled (and I have failed) to think of anything new I didn’t hate.</p>

<h3 id="films-ie-long-form-storytelling">Films (i.e. long form storytelling)</h3>

<p>The M word for films makes me feel a bit nauseous, like people get about words like “touch” and “moist” so I don’t say it. I think it might be because it sounds like something a toddler would say if they didn’t know the right word? Anyway, I hate it.</p>

<p>I’m a big motorsports fan and I think women are people so of course I watched and loathed that F1 film. It was painful to endure and I don’t understand why through the editing process no one said “this is embarrassing and we need to make this better” but I’m sure it earned plenty of cash.</p>

<p>The live action remake of Lilo and Stitch was unneccesary but basically fine and I thought the performance of the little girl was great. Shame not to get Ving Rames and I’m not sure why they added the portal gun from the Portal games but I like the Portal games and it was fun.</p>

<p>The other day we saw the Spongebob film and there were things about it which were pretty alright. I expected that to be a miserable couple of hours for me sat there but the nods to Greek myths and Mark Hamill was enough to keep me engaged.</p>

<p>I’m sure I saw some other new films but I don’t remember them. Honestly I don’t really care about films (outside of Takeshi Kitano gangster films) and if you want film recommendations then probably ask someone else.</p>

<h3 id="something-positive-though">Something positive though</h3>

<p>There is some incredible work going on by people who don’t have the BBC or Netflix funding them but they just have something to say. I’m thinking of people like Josh Johnson, whose output has been just incredible through the year. Television and cinema are basically over but we don’t need the gatekeepers, just a camera and some time.</p>

<h2 id="motorsport">Motorsport</h2>

<p>I felt like 2025 was quite a sad year for motorsport in general. The FIA and NASCAR organisations have their reputations absolutely in the toilet now. This doesn’t take away from some amazing performances by drivers and teams though.</p>

<p><img src="/public/img/truck.jpg" alt="Truck." />
<em>British Truck Racing Championship. Brands Hatch.</em></p>

<p>Go and see some motorsport near you. It’s a great day out!</p>

<h3 id="single-seaters">Single seaters</h3>

<p>McLaren muddled over the line but the drivers need to tell the team that the perception of fairness is not as important as winning. At times it felt like Mac strategy was designed to give Max a chance!</p>

<p>Indycar never looked particularly close this year. I didn’t much like Will Buxton on the coverage. I’m glad Penske had such rotten results but otherwise there was little to be excited about.</p>

<p>Formula 2 was a mixed bag. There were some fun races but apart from the champ Fornaroli the whole field had such inconsistent performance that I can’t see any of these guys being world champions of the future. Dunne really faded but an absolute shocker was Gabriele Minì. F3 was much the same. I wonder if it’s because the costs are so high and the seasons so long.</p>

<p>I didn’t really follow British F4 this year or regional F3/F4 championships.</p>

<h3 id="endurance-sports-cars-etc">Endurance, sports cars, etc.</h3>

<p>IMSA was great this year, full of excitement and great coverage. I am super into the AO Racing team with their dinosaur themed cars and getting the kids excited, making great merch and then throwing everything at the performances. The Vasser Sullivan team gets my respect too, turning up year after year with that ancient Lexus GT3 (that car was launched in 2014!) and achieving great things.</p>

<p>As a bonus IMSA has the best support series on the planet, the MX-5 cup, as well as the best commentary team in John and Shea.</p>

<p>It’s a great time to get into enduros as Verstappen draws attention to the Nurburgring and more manufacturers join the WEC.</p>

<p>People ask me how you enjoy endurance racing. It’s a strange thing to get in to! Basically you pop it up on a screen and get on with what you’re doing, looking over when you hear some excitement, tuning in and out as you please. It’s like test cricket a bit. You can sit and take in an hour here and there but you don’t sit and stare for the full event. Maybe I’ll write a full essay about how to enjoy enduros but that’s the gist. Daytona soon!</p>

<h3 id="rally-rallycross">Rally, rallycross</h3>

<p>The WRC was really hot this year. I’ve never been a big fan of watching rallies. They are great to drive in but they aren’t made for television. The WRC was great this year. I’m worried about next year with two of the top drivers quitting.</p>

<p>Rallycross had such a terrible year. It’s my favourite racing format but there just seems to be no way of making it sustainable. I don’t understand how no one makes a success of it, because RX is perfect for TV and really fun for more casual fans. RIP to WorldRX, Nitrocross, Extreme E.</p>

<p>But let’s not worry about that right now. Just make sure you’re watching the British RX and also RallyX.</p>

<p>Now the W2RC is the craziest thing in the world I’m sure and I am still in shock at Nassar losing the title over a timing technicality. The Dakar is coming up and you need to make sure you’re catching those daily highlights.</p>

<h3 id="random-car-bits">Random car bits</h3>

<p>I was glad Tom Ingram got it done in the BTCC. One of the nicest racing drivers I’ve met, so much time for everyone. I remember when he was posting on his Facebook every week trying desperately to get helo funding the next weekend of racing.</p>

<p>The British Hillclimbing has been great fun. You’ve got to get to an event near you, it’s so much fun in person. The commentary team on youtube are excellent too.</p>

<p>I guess read this if you haven’t: <a href="https://nicoboyce.com/wheels/2025/08/10/racing-worth-watching/">Racing worth watching</a></p>

<h2 id="stop-reading-here">Stop reading here</h2>

<p>This is the end of the article (I might start putting this on everything I write)</p>]]></content><author><name>Nico Beastie Boyce</name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[wow that was a time wasn’t it So yes today is the LAST DAY OF THE YEAR and so here are some thoughts which I have had on various topics. Do you agree? Do you disagree? That’s okay! Music, sounds, etc I guess for a lot of people 2025 was about waiting in virtual queues hoping to get tickets to big stadium shows from lowest common denominator pop acts. I’m not mad at you if you are in to that, I’m just disappointed and let’s not speak about it further. We saw some really great stuff. Have A Nice Life. Divide And Dissolve. Earth. The Beta Band! High On Fire (plus incredible supports including Castle Rat) and I’m sure I’m forgetting so many excellent other bands. Queens of the Stone Age a couple of times. I’ve heard people say don’t meet your heroes. They need to choose their heroes better. I’ve met pretty much all of my musical idols and they were almost all absolutely lovely. Dylan Carlson of Earth. How about new music? So 2025 was a year where artists whose work I had been enjoying over the last few years released records which made me go “oh okay, that’s a shame.” Here are some of those: Earl Sweatshirt Simz Ikonika FKA Twigs JPEGMAFIA Divide And Dissolve Princess Nokia Yaya Bey Masters of Reality None of these were bad! They were all fine but just not super great. Anyone who had Eusexua on their best-of lists honestly probably just hasn’t recently revisited the best stuff Madonna and Bjork did in the 1990s. While collating this list I made a note that I need to put some more time in to the newest Clipping and Kae Tempest records. My favourite new record this year was PinkPanteress mixtape Fancy That and my favourite new song of the year was Music by Underscores and nothing else really came close to those choices for me. Finally I’ve got to say “go and listen to Esdeekid” if you’re not yet in on that thing. Live highlights? My favourite performance I got to experience this year is a bit more tough. I’m going to pick individual songs from shows, why not. The Bees Made Honey in the Lion’s Skull by Earth at the Electric Ballroom was like the whole world was revolving around the incredible patience of drummer Adrienne. Teased out over what felt like hours, this rendition of this track was so powerful I don’t know how we made it home afterwards. Queens of the Stone Age, Long Slow Goodbye at the Royal Albert Hall. I didn’t have Josh Homme waving a hatchett around and Matt Berry pulling out all the stops on the monstrous RAH organ on my bingo card for the year. The Beta Band, Dry the Rain. This was at the Roundhouse. It felt like a strange moment in my life. The two decades since their last shows, one of the first proper gigs I made it to, all of that seemed forgiven in that moment. TV, cinema, audiovisual media I am always saying I don’t feel like film is a great way to tell a story. Nothing in 2025 has changed my view on that. I have really struggled (and I have failed) to think of anything new I didn’t hate. Films (i.e. long form storytelling) The M word for films makes me feel a bit nauseous, like people get about words like “touch” and “moist” so I don’t say it. I think it might be because it sounds like something a toddler would say if they didn’t know the right word? Anyway, I hate it. I’m a big motorsports fan and I think women are people so of course I watched and loathed that F1 film. It was painful to endure and I don’t understand why through the editing process no one said “this is embarrassing and we need to make this better” but I’m sure it earned plenty of cash. The live action remake of Lilo and Stitch was unneccesary but basically fine and I thought the performance of the little girl was great. Shame not to get Ving Rames and I’m not sure why they added the portal gun from the Portal games but I like the Portal games and it was fun. The other day we saw the Spongebob film and there were things about it which were pretty alright. I expected that to be a miserable couple of hours for me sat there but the nods to Greek myths and Mark Hamill was enough to keep me engaged. I’m sure I saw some other new films but I don’t remember them. Honestly I don’t really care about films (outside of Takeshi Kitano gangster films) and if you want film recommendations then probably ask someone else. Something positive though There is some incredible work going on by people who don’t have the BBC or Netflix funding them but they just have something to say. I’m thinking of people like Josh Johnson, whose output has been just incredible through the year. Television and cinema are basically over but we don’t need the gatekeepers, just a camera and some time. Motorsport I felt like 2025 was quite a sad year for motorsport in general. The FIA and NASCAR organisations have their reputations absolutely in the toilet now. This doesn’t take away from some amazing performances by drivers and teams though. British Truck Racing Championship. Brands Hatch. Go and see some motorsport near you. It’s a great day out! Single seaters McLaren muddled over the line but the drivers need to tell the team that the perception of fairness is not as important as winning. At times it felt like Mac strategy was designed to give Max a chance! Indycar never looked particularly close this year. I didn’t much like Will Buxton on the coverage. I’m glad Penske had such rotten results but otherwise there was little to be excited about. Formula 2 was a mixed bag. There were some fun races but apart from the champ Fornaroli the whole field had such inconsistent performance that I can’t see any of these guys being world champions of the future. Dunne really faded but an absolute shocker was Gabriele Minì. F3 was much the same. I wonder if it’s because the costs are so high and the seasons so long. I didn’t really follow British F4 this year or regional F3/F4 championships. Endurance, sports cars, etc. IMSA was great this year, full of excitement and great coverage. I am super into the AO Racing team with their dinosaur themed cars and getting the kids excited, making great merch and then throwing everything at the performances. The Vasser Sullivan team gets my respect too, turning up year after year with that ancient Lexus GT3 (that car was launched in 2014!) and achieving great things. As a bonus IMSA has the best support series on the planet, the MX-5 cup, as well as the best commentary team in John and Shea. It’s a great time to get into enduros as Verstappen draws attention to the Nurburgring and more manufacturers join the WEC. People ask me how you enjoy endurance racing. It’s a strange thing to get in to! Basically you pop it up on a screen and get on with what you’re doing, looking over when you hear some excitement, tuning in and out as you please. It’s like test cricket a bit. You can sit and take in an hour here and there but you don’t sit and stare for the full event. Maybe I’ll write a full essay about how to enjoy enduros but that’s the gist. Daytona soon! Rally, rallycross The WRC was really hot this year. I’ve never been a big fan of watching rallies. They are great to drive in but they aren’t made for television. The WRC was great this year. I’m worried about next year with two of the top drivers quitting. Rallycross had such a terrible year. It’s my favourite racing format but there just seems to be no way of making it sustainable. I don’t understand how no one makes a success of it, because RX is perfect for TV and really fun for more casual fans. RIP to WorldRX, Nitrocross, Extreme E. But let’s not worry about that right now. Just make sure you’re watching the British RX and also RallyX. Now the W2RC is the craziest thing in the world I’m sure and I am still in shock at Nassar losing the title over a timing technicality. The Dakar is coming up and you need to make sure you’re catching those daily highlights. Random car bits I was glad Tom Ingram got it done in the BTCC. One of the nicest racing drivers I’ve met, so much time for everyone. I remember when he was posting on his Facebook every week trying desperately to get helo funding the next weekend of racing. The British Hillclimbing has been great fun. You’ve got to get to an event near you, it’s so much fun in person. The commentary team on youtube are excellent too. I guess read this if you haven’t: Racing worth watching Stop reading here This is the end of the article (I might start putting this on everything I write)]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Nico vanity shots of 2025</title><link href="https://nicoboyce.com/snaps/2025/12/29/nico-vanity-shots-of-2025/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Nico vanity shots of 2025" /><published>2025-12-29T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2025-12-29T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://nicoboyce.com/snaps/2025/12/29/nico-vanity-shots-of-2025</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://nicoboyce.com/snaps/2025/12/29/nico-vanity-shots-of-2025/"><![CDATA[<p><img src="/public/img/nbb/nbb-bmx.jpg" alt="BMX." />
<em>BMX.</em></p>

<p><img src="/public/img/nbb/nbb-cold.jpg" alt="Cold." />
<em>Cold.</em></p>

<p><img src="/public/img/nbb/nbb-como.jpg" alt="Como." />
<em>Como.</em></p>

<p><img src="/public/img/nbb/nbb-conference.jpg" alt="Conference." />
<em>Conference.</em></p>

<p><img src="/public/img/nbb/nbb-gb.jpg" alt="GB." />
<em>Geckoboard. <a href="www.youtube.com/watch?v=rN7V9Q1XHvY">Watch us here</a></em></p>

<p><img src="/public/img/nbb/nbb-london.jpg" alt="London." />
<em>London.</em></p>

<p><img src="/public/img/nbb/nbb-photography.jpg" alt="Photography." />
<em>Photography.</em></p>

<p><img src="/public/img/nbb/nbb-shorn.jpg" alt="Shorn." />
<em>Shorn.</em></p>]]></content><author><name>Nico Beastie Boyce</name></author><category term="snaps" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[BMX. Cold. Como. Conference. Geckoboard. Watch us here London. Photography. Shorn.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Brands Hatch camera showdown</title><link href="https://nicoboyce.com/wheels/2025/11/09/brands-hatch-camera-showdown/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Brands Hatch camera showdown" /><published>2025-11-09T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2025-11-09T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://nicoboyce.com/wheels/2025/11/09/brands-hatch-camera-showdown</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://nicoboyce.com/wheels/2025/11/09/brands-hatch-camera-showdown/"><![CDATA[<p>We took a bunch of photography gear to Brands Hatch. One of the cameras was my current favourite toy, this F601 with 75-300mm.</p>

<p><img src="/public/img/brands-hatch/nikonf601.jpg" alt="Nikon F601 camera." />
<em>Snap snap!</em></p>

<p>Representing modernity we had a Fuji XS20, Sigma 16-300mm. In the middle we had a Nikon D3300, 70-300mm. Can you guess which photo was taken with which camera?</p>

<p><img src="/public/img/brands-hatch/druids.jpeg" alt="Druids corner action." />
<em>TCRs struggle for grip at Druids.</em></p>

<p><img src="/public/img/brands-hatch/teeth.jpg" alt="TCR teeth." />
<em>Tasty TCR.</em></p>

<p><img src="/public/img/brands-hatch/minis.jpg" alt="Mini racing." />
<em>Greasy conditions and front wheel drive means endless understeer.</em></p>

<p><img src="/public/img/brands-hatch/saxo.jpg" alt="Saxo on track." />
<em>Saxo appeal.</em></p>

<p><img src="/public/img/brands-hatch/truck.jpg" alt="Racing truck." />
<em>Heavy metal.</em></p>

<p>If you’re looking to get some film developed, give <a href="https://www.thefilmsafe.co.uk/?hellofromnicoboycedotcom">The Film Safe</a> a go. Top people and great results.</p>]]></content><author><name>Nico Beastie Boyce</name></author><category term="wheels" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[We took a bunch of photography gear to Brands Hatch. One of the cameras was my current favourite toy, this F601 with 75-300mm. Snap snap! Representing modernity we had a Fuji XS20, Sigma 16-300mm. In the middle we had a Nikon D3300, 70-300mm. Can you guess which photo was taken with which camera? TCRs struggle for grip at Druids. Tasty TCR. Greasy conditions and front wheel drive means endless understeer. Saxo appeal. Heavy metal. If you’re looking to get some film developed, give The Film Safe a go. Top people and great results.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Top straight white guy jobs in ‘25</title><link href="https://nicoboyce.com/2025/09/23/top-straight-white-guy-jobs-25/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Top straight white guy jobs in ‘25" /><published>2025-09-23T00:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2025-09-23T00:00:00+01:00</updated><id>https://nicoboyce.com/2025/09/23/top-straight-white-guy-jobs-25</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://nicoboyce.com/2025/09/23/top-straight-white-guy-jobs-25/"><![CDATA[<h3 id="or-how-to-unleash-that-secret-talent-youre-sure-you-have-somewhere-big-guy">or How to unleash that secret talent you’re sure you have somewhere, big guy</h3>

<p>Doing things is hard. Making new things requires understanding existing things. Skills take time to develop, tools need to be mastered, creativity requires imagination. Who can be arsed? Certainly not the straight white guys of the internet!</p>

<p>Here are some things they can fall upwards into, despite everything about them.<!--excerpt-end--></p>

<h4 id="looking-at-things">Looking at things</h4>

<p>This is a great place to start because the barrier to entry is almost zero. You’re probably reading this on a thing which can take photos, so that saves any initial expenditure. Later you will need a Leica for the little red circle on the front. The process:</p>

<ol>
  <li>See somthing</li>
  <li>Point the camera at it</li>
  <li>Write a vague caption not related to the image “Sometimes the first step is the hardest” or “When the real enemy is within” etc</li>
  <li>Buy gear.</li>
</ol>

<p><img src="/public/img/snap.jpg" alt="Shooting." />
<em>What a poseur.</em></p>

<p>There’s no point where money is likely to fall out but if you grow your hair a bit floppy and tell a lot of people you are a photographer, maybe someone dumb and pretty will let you look at them through a lens. This is literally the dream of every white guy with a Leica, to become a pornographer without having to learn anything or hire sex workers.</p>

<h4 id="listening-to-things">Listening to things</h4>

<p>Music reviews used to be useful in 1999 when CDs were like £15 (which is probably £40 in 2025 sterling) and your pocket money covered maybe one or two a month. But it’s not 1999 now and everyone has access to basically all of the music basically all of the time. No one needs to read reviews to decide whether they’ll listen to Showbiz or Performance and Cocktails or Californication. You can quickly flick through all three and be judgemental (overwrought juvenile psuedointellectualism, unimaginitive and unambitious, overproduced overwritten earache, respectively) in a shorter time than it would take to find the right issues of NME.</p>

<p>Nevertheless that guy Anthony Fantano is over there and Rick Beato is that way and Christgau still exists (why?) and you could join them if you can bitch your way into a position of presumed authority on a form of media which essentially exists as a utility rather than luxury now.</p>

<p>See also: that guy booted from comedy rock one hit wonders the Darkness. Youtube suggests him all the time but I never click it. Will it learn?</p>

<h4 id="playing-video-games">Playing video games</h4>

<p>Remember how you were always being told to get off your arse and do something because playing video games doesn’t pay the bills? But now she has gone and you watch people you don’t know play games and people give them cash all day! Repeat after me: Fuck you Michelle, you’ll soon see, just as soon as I get some LED triangles for my wall and get good at Rocket League.</p>

<h4 id="literally-just-whinge-about-stuff">Literally just whinge about stuff</h4>

<p>Podcasts are back again, again, though now no one has ipods or uses rss but who cares, grab a mic and make sounds!</p>

<p><img src="/public/img/recording.jpeg" alt="Talking." />
<em>Talking.</em></p>

<p>You can combine this with anything else (or nothing) so long as you’re talking. Someone is bound to want to listen!</p>]]></content><author><name>Nico Beastie Boyce</name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[or How to unleash that secret talent you’re sure you have somewhere, big guy Doing things is hard. Making new things requires understanding existing things. Skills take time to develop, tools need to be mastered, creativity requires imagination. Who can be arsed? Certainly not the straight white guys of the internet! Here are some things they can fall upwards into, despite everything about them.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Structures</title><link href="https://nicoboyce.com/snaps/2025/08/23/structures/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Structures" /><published>2025-08-23T00:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2025-08-23T00:00:00+01:00</updated><id>https://nicoboyce.com/snaps/2025/08/23/structures</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://nicoboyce.com/snaps/2025/08/23/structures/"><![CDATA[<p><img src="/public/img/lecco.jpg" alt="Lecco." />
<em>Lecco.</em></p>

<p><img src="/public/img/balconies.jpg" alt="Balconies." />
<em>Balconies.</em></p>

<p><img src="/public/img/wedge.jpg" alt="Wedge." />
<em>Wedge.</em></p>

<p><img src="/public/img/towers.jpg" alt="Towers." />
<em>Towers.</em></p>]]></content><author><name>Nico Beastie Boyce</name></author><category term="snaps" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lecco. Balconies. Wedge. Towers.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Italian animals</title><link href="https://nicoboyce.com/snaps/2025/08/23/italian-animals/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Italian animals" /><published>2025-08-23T00:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2025-08-23T00:00:00+01:00</updated><id>https://nicoboyce.com/snaps/2025/08/23/italian-animals</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://nicoboyce.com/snaps/2025/08/23/italian-animals/"><![CDATA[<p><img src="/public/img/halo.jpg" alt="Halo." />
<em>Halo.</em></p>

<p><img src="/public/img/tucked.jpeg" alt="Tucked." />
<em>Tucked.</em></p>

<p><img src="/public/img/egret.jpg" alt="Egret." />
<em>Egret.</em></p>]]></content><author><name>Nico Beastie Boyce</name></author><category term="snaps" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Halo. Tucked. Egret.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Classy travellers</title><link href="https://nicoboyce.com/wheels/2025/08/23/classy-travellers/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Classy travellers" /><published>2025-08-23T00:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2025-08-23T00:00:00+01:00</updated><id>https://nicoboyce.com/wheels/2025/08/23/classy-travellers</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://nicoboyce.com/wheels/2025/08/23/classy-travellers/"><![CDATA[<p><img src="/public/img/teeth.jpg" alt="Teeth." />
<em>Teeth.</em></p>

<p><img src="/public/img/chunk.jpeg" alt="Chunk." />
<em>Chunk.</em></p>]]></content><author><name>Nico Beastie Boyce</name></author><category term="wheels" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Teeth. Chunk.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Visit to Museo della Seta di Como</title><link href="https://nicoboyce.com/snaps/2025/08/23/visit-to-museo-della-seta-di-como/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Visit to Museo della Seta di Como" /><published>2025-08-23T00:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2025-08-23T00:00:00+01:00</updated><id>https://nicoboyce.com/snaps/2025/08/23/visit-to-museo-della-seta-di-como</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://nicoboyce.com/snaps/2025/08/23/visit-to-museo-della-seta-di-como/"><![CDATA[<p><img src="/public/img/silk/silk1.jpeg" alt="Silk weaving machine." /></p>

<p><img src="/public/img/silk/silk2.jpeg" alt="Silk threads." /></p>

<p><img src="/public/img/silk/silk3.jpeg" alt="Vintage loom." /></p>

<p><img src="/public/img/silk/silk4.jpeg" alt="Silk production tools." /></p>

<p><img src="/public/img/silk/silk5.jpeg" alt="Museum display." /></p>

<p><img src="/public/img/silk/silk6.jpeg" alt="Historic machinery." /></p>

<p><img src="/public/img/silk/silk7.jpeg" alt="Silk processing equipment." /></p>

<p><img src="/public/img/silk/silk8.jpeg" alt="Workshop interior." /></p>]]></content><author><name>Nico Beastie Boyce</name></author><category term="snaps" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[]]></summary></entry></feed>